[
  {
    "date": "2021-08-12",
    "title": "ARMY QUARANTINE CENTRES: Where Feeling helps Healing",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Even though the word 'Quarantine' was not familiar to us in Sri Lanka before the COVID-19 pandemic, it has a long history around the globe during various time periods with the emergence of different diseases.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/army-quarantine-centres-where-feeling-helps-healing/ar-AANdz0d",
    "url_hash": "e9fdbabb04e97a43da14d859032cd9ab",
    "ut": 1628727284,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-12",
    "title": "SLT-MOBITEL 'Sip Nena Dayada' ensures 'free access to connectivity' for students",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "SLT-MOBITEL, the National ICT, Telecommunications and Mobile Services Provider, joined hands with the Sri Sambodhi Foundation to provide free access and connectivity for students participating in online learning,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/slt-mobitel-sip-nena-dayada-ensures-free-access-to-connectivity-for-students/ar-AANdz0m",
    "url_hash": "6f83cf04aaea54589ae493c4a85ef774",
    "ut": 1628727284,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SLT-MOBITEL",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the National ICT, Telecommunications and Mobile Services Provider",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sri Sambodhi Foundation",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-12",
    "title": "Indian cricket tour yields $ 14.5 million",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "India's recent cricket tour of Sri Lanka has resulted in a $ 14.5 million revenue to Sri Lanka Cricket (SLC), SLC Secretary Mohan de Silva said. \"According to the FTP (Future Tours Program) the tour was only for 3 ODIs,",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/indian-cricket-tour-yields-14-5-million/",
    "url_hash": "b3df9d087c00869a951f6e388636b738",
    "ut": 1628727284,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "$ 14.5 million",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Cricket",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SLC",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Mohan de Silva",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "3",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          47
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-12",
    "title": "Set-Back For Tamil Family Fighting To Avoid Deportation",
    "source": "www.triplem.com.au",
    "snippet": "A blow for a Biloela asylum seeker family with The High Court's rejection on Thursday to approve a special leave request for their youngest daughter's visa application. The Tamil family hit the headlines and our hearts back in 2019 when the family based in rural Queensland were sent into detention on Christmas Island Then after the youngest daughter Tharnicaa became unwell with a blood infection and was hospitalised in Perth,",
    "url": "https://www.triplem.com.au/story/set-back-for-tamil-family-fighting-to-avoid-deportation-181126",
    "url_hash": "e4d212a2156aabf202c59300c64cd43e",
    "ut": 1628733764,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Biloela",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The High Court's",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Thursday",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Tamil",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2019",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Queensland",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          49
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Perth",
        "start_end": [
          72,
          73
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]