[
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "SLFP turns 70",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The Sri Lanka Freedom Party (SLFP) marks its 70th anniversary today.The SLFP has arranged an island wide blood donation campaign and a commemorative ceremony which will be held virtually due to the current COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/slfp-turns-70/ar-AAO09di",
    "url_hash": "6f6b7b808b63de7cfdbfc2d05239657b",
    "ut": 1630541289,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Sri Lanka Freedom Party",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "70th",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SLFP",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Recognizing vital role of SMEs in Sri Lanka's Tourism Sector",
    "source": "a.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The Foreign Ministry of Sri Lanka in collaboration with Sri Lanka Tourism recently hosted a virtual business to business (B2B) interactive session with the Member states of the Conference on Interaction and Confidence-Building Measures in Asia (CICA) with the aim of enhancing tourism cooperation in the region.",
    "url": "http://a.msn.com/0F/en-xl/AAO07gy",
    "url_hash": "81ec4d71c169e9e4a1d283c6759e8a98",
    "ut": 1630541308,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Foreign Ministry of Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Conference on Interaction and Confidence-Building Measures",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          38
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Asia",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          40
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Kandy Perahera live streaming attracts 16K global viewers",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The global live streaming of the Kandy Esala Perahera that was facilitated by Sri Lanka Tourism this year reached nearly 16,000 viewers across the globe making the online promotion effort during the pandemic a success,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/kandy-perahera-live-streaming-attracts-16k-global-viewers/ar-AAO03ZH",
    "url_hash": "3e868646fbeffd84449aafb3ce84e439",
    "ut": 1630541308,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "the Kandy Esala Perahera",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "this year",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "nearly 16,000",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "CFA Society Sri Lanka launches 'Equity Analyst Training' with Acuity Knowledge Partners",
    "source": "www.ft.lk",
    "snippet": "CFA Society Sri Lanka announced its virtual course - 'Equity Analyst Training' together with its Training Partner Acuity Knowledge Partners. With the inaugural course commencement scheduled for 24 September, the program is already gaining popularity ...",
    "url": "https://www.ft.lk/financial-services/CFA-Society-Sri-Lanka-launches--Equity-Analyst-Training--with-Acuity-Knowledge-Partners/42-722524",
    "url_hash": "bb2daa810a2fddc7a21c709dab1a627c",
    "ut": 1630541333,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "CFA Society Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "24 September",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "CSE world's highest gainer in August, trading at a 40% discount to peers",
    "source": "www.ft.lk",
    "snippet": "Softlogic Stockbrokers said yesterday that the Colombo Stock Exchange (CSE) was the highest gainer globally in August and second-best performer year-to-date (YTD), trading at a 40% discount to peers.",
    "url": "https://www.ft.lk/front-page/CSE-world-s-highest-gainer-in-August-trading-at-a-40-discount-to-peers/44-722545",
    "url_hash": "341c65f4fb3c7a48a0a03ec469ce5446",
    "ut": 1630541526,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Softlogic Stockbrokers",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Colombo Stock Exchange",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "CSE",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "August",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "second",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "year-to-date",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERCENT",
        "text": "40%",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "SLFP: TRUE CIVIC NATIONALISM",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Very few social forces have managed to live above the deeply dividing ethnic and religious politics of recent Sri Lanka. The Sri Lanka Freedom Party (SLFP) is the only national ruling party that had actively accommodated all identities in Sri Lanka and adopted that as a core value of its political operation.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/slfp-true-civic-nationalism/ar-AAO027n",
    "url_hash": "9ce97c128cfa59067cd3b65992645300",
    "ut": 1630541665,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Sri Lanka Freedom Party",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          44
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Recognizing vital role of SMEs in Sri Lanka's Tourism Sector",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The Foreign Ministry of Sri Lanka in collaboration with Sri Lanka Tourism recently hosted a virtual business to business (B2B) interactive session with the Member states of the Conference on Interaction and Confidence-Building Measures in Asia (CICA) with the aim of enhancing tourism cooperation in the region.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/recognizing-vital-role-of-smes-in-sri-lanka-s-tourism-sector/ar-AAO07gy",
    "url_hash": "cdaa38d18f419eb60888bd338b9e5d2f",
    "ut": 1630541665,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Foreign Ministry of Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Conference on Interaction and Confidence-Building Measures",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          38
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Asia",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          40
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "SLFP turns 70",
    "source": "a.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The Sri Lanka Freedom Party (SLFP) marks its 70th anniversary today.The SLFP has arranged an island wide blood donation campaign and a commemorative ceremony which will be held virtually due to the current COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "url": "http://a.msn.com/0F/en-xl/AAO09di",
    "url_hash": "12aa0f3952d0d040b5035a36ca12dc0d",
    "ut": 1630541665,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Sri Lanka Freedom Party",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "70th",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SLFP",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka prints Rs17.6bn after dysfunctional bill, bond auctions, sugar seized",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has printed 6.0 billion rupees after a bond auction failed to sell sufficient securities to the public amid price controls, on top of an earlier bill auction, data shows.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-prints-rs17-6bn-after-dysfunctional-bill-bond-auctions-sugar-seized-85685/",
    "url_hash": "4146022514c43203d85c003c566fb6a6",
    "ut": 1630541685,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "6.0 billion",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka prints Rs17.6bn after dysfunctional bill, bond auctions",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has printed 6.0 billion rupees after a bond auction failed to sell sufficient securities to the public amid price controls, on top of an earlier bill auction, data shows.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-prints-rs17-6bn-after-dysfunctional-bill-bond-auctions-85685/",
    "url_hash": "a497db0e965ef961edf95f4ab5dbcc73",
    "ut": 1630541685,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "6.0 billion",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka prints Rs18bn after bill, bond auction dysfunctions",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has printed 6.0 billion rupees after a bond auction failed to sell sufficient securities to the public amid price controls, on top of an earlier bill auction, data shows.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-prints-rs18bn-after-bill-bond-auction-dysfunctions-85685/",
    "url_hash": "5e940fe6fc773c0466c587f68648f4dd",
    "ut": 1630542501,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "6.0 billion",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "BOI registered company among those hoarding sugar",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "A company registered with the Board of Investment (BOI) was among a number of institutions found to be hoarding sugar yesterday, Daily Mirror learns. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/BOI-registered-company-among-those-hoarding-sugar/342-219500",
    "url_hash": "255a00dc3c30ca87d034c9bb4581ed02",
    "ut": 1630544875,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Board of Investment",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "BOI",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Daily Mirror",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Covid pandemic cannot be overcome by locking down the country, DDG Health",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "While claiming that the Covid pandemic could not be overcome by locking down the country, Deputy Director General of Health Services Dr. Hemantha Herath said yesterday what was important was the people's cooperation and their adherence to health practices.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Covid-pandemic-cannot-be-overcome-by-locking-down-the-country-DDG-Health/108-219499",
    "url_hash": "2d04698a5550aefd83b0df0939b75eff",
    "ut": 1630544899,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Covid",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Health Services",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hemantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Ivermectin tablets for COVID-19: Stop using it as no evidence yet, experts warn",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Senior medical experts yesterday warned the public against the use of Ivermectin tablets which are being prescribed by some health consultants to prevent or fight the COVID-19 virus, saying a local study was presently underway to study this drug but it had not been approved.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Ivermectin-tablets-for-COVID-19:-Stop-using-it-as-no-evidence-yet--experts-warn/342-219498",
    "url_hash": "0db6e6d98697ab8d0a3d7383e5463803",
    "ut": 1630544899,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Ivermectin",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "BOI registered company among those hoarding sugar",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "A company registered with the Board of Investment (BOI) was among a number of institutions found to be hoarding sugar yesterday, Daily Mirror learns. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/BOI-registered-company-among-those-hoarding-sugar/108-219500",
    "url_hash": "b80190bdc022e93af6298542ab331da3",
    "ut": 1630544899,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Board of Investment",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "BOI",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Daily Mirror",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Ivermectin tablets for COVID-19: Stop using it as no evidence yet, experts warn",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Senior medical experts yesterday warned the public against the use of Ivermectin tablets which are being prescribed by some health consultants to prevent or fight the COVID-19 virus, saying a local study was presently underway to study this drug but it had not been approved.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/top_story/Ivermectin-tablets-for-COVID-19-Stop-using-it-as-no-evidence-yet-experts-warn/155-219498",
    "url_hash": "be4662728af1ecf06b2ce9eac12c099e",
    "ut": 1630544900,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Ivermectin",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Ivermectin tablets for COVID-19: Stop using it as no evidence yet, experts warn",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Senior medical experts yesterday warned the public against the use of Ivermectin tablets which are being prescribed by some health consultants to prevent or fight the COVID-19 virus, saying a local study was presently underway to study this drug but it had not been approved.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Ivermectin-tablets-for-COVID-19-Stop-using-it-as-no-evidence-yet-experts-warn/342-219498",
    "url_hash": "8ff098be9115a857efd5839f471dd6ec",
    "ut": 1630544912,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Ivermectin",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Covid pandemic cannot be overcome by locking down the country, DDG Health",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "While claiming that the Covid pandemic could not be overcome by locking down the country, Deputy Director General of Health Services Dr. Hemantha Herath said yesterday what was important was the people's cooperation and their adherence to health practices.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Covid-pandemic-cannot-be-overcome-by-locking-down-the-country-DDG-Health/342-219499",
    "url_hash": "06ca9abd8a0c6975ad7140b349471458",
    "ut": 1630545115,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Covid",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Health Services",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hemantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Coronavirus death toll in Sri Lanka crosses the 9000 mark",
    "source": "menafn.com",
    "snippet": "(MENAFN - Colombo Gazette) The coronavirus death toll in Sri Lanka crossed the 9000 mark today. The Ministry of Health said that another 194 deaths linked to the virus were confirmed today.",
    "url": "https://menafn.com/1102722074/Coronavirus-death-toll-in-Sri-Lanka-crosses-the-9000-mark",
    "url_hash": "3025a73cf8bc1dc67b8eebb5b45e72c1",
    "ut": 1630545649,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PRODUCT",
        "text": "9000",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Ministry of Health",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "194",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Coastal belt in Ernakulam on high alert for Sri Lankans",
    "source": "www.newindianexpress.com",
    "snippet": "Alert says 13 of them may travel to Pakistan from harbours in dist or Alappuzha; security audit identifies several vulnerabilities on coast",
    "url": "https://www.newindianexpress.com/cities/kochi/2021/sep/02/coastal-belt-in-district-on-high-alert-for-sri-lankans-2353030.html",
    "url_hash": "cea08e40710a8b25b8114fc6b7f25287",
    "ut": 1630546120,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Alert",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "13",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Alappuzha",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "South African variant: WHO is yet to characterize it as variant of concern",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The World Health Organization (WHO) says the coronavirus variant C.1.2 is not yet considered a variant of concern (VOC). ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/South-African-variant-WHO-is-yet-to-characterize-it-as-variant-of-concern/108-219502",
    "url_hash": "26ac8b02cf588f33411279225f8f54e3",
    "ut": 1630548499,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The World Health Organization",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "C.1.2",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Spells of showers expected in many parts of the island",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "Several spells of showers or thundershowers are expected in Western, Sabaragamuwa and North-western provinces as well as in Kandy, Nuwara-Eliya, Galle and Matara districts, says the Department of Mete",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news/76605/spells-of-showers-expected-in-many-parts-of-the-island",
    "url_hash": "11f4160a462097602ac5a18498fac33f",
    "ut": 1630548508,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Western",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sabaragamuwa",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Kandy",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Nuwara-Eliya",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Galle",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Matara",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Department of Mete",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Spells of showers expected in many parts of the island",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "Several spells of showers or thundershowers are expected in Western, Sabaragamuwa and North-western provinces as well as in Kandy, Nuwara-Eliya, Galle and Matara districts, says the Department of Mete",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news.php?nid=76605",
    "url_hash": "b88b214d7a76bab3cb6d38fa1c7df6c0",
    "ut": 1630548650,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Western",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sabaragamuwa",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Kandy",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Nuwara-Eliya",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Galle",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Matara",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Department of Mete",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "China accuses US of politicising global response to COVID-19",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "The recent U.S. Intelligence Report on COVID-19 Origins has the ugly agenda of politicising the global response to COVID-19 when unity and cooperation is key, Chinese Ambassador to Sri Lanka, Qi Zhenhong said yesterday,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/china-accuses-us-of-politicising-global-response-to-covid-19/",
    "url_hash": "9b0612fbf64714e7b62e7255ead1d566",
    "ut": 1630551642,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "U.S. Intelligence Report",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Chinese",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Qi Zhenhong",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Nishantha: The coach behind historic Paralympic gold",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Reemus Fernando   A coach plays a vital role in an athlete's success. When it comes to track and field sports, a coach can make or break the career of an athlete. It is the coach's specific training plan that helps the athlete peak at the right time to produce his best.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/nishantha-the-coach-behind-historic-paralympic-gold/",
    "url_hash": "050728e17c3a381265c10a0d5c4d3b40",
    "ut": 1630551868,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Reemus Fernando   ",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Samsung introduces Samsung Smart Keyboard Trio 500 in Sri Lanka",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "In a mobile-first world, learning and working while on the go has become commonplace. When you need the efficiency and comfort of typing on a physical keyboard but don't want to carry around your laptop,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/samsung-introduces-samsung-smart-keyboard-trio-500-in-sri-lanka/",
    "url_hash": "2970313e48beb4a4d954a455b541445e",
    "ut": 1630552089,
    "ent_info_list": []
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka expecting nearly 12 million COVID vaccines within next two months",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka will receive approximately 12 million doses of COVID-19 vaccines within the next two months, the State Pharmaceuticals Corporation (SPC) says",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news/76606/sri-lanka-expecting-nearly-12-million-covid-vaccines-within-next-two-months",
    "url_hash": "ceb56a7a7f6de369b438ec73dc115306",
    "ut": 1630552111,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "approximately 12 million",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the next two months",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the State Pharmaceuticals Corporation",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Minister Pathirana correct only on low diesel prices in Sri Lanka",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The minister claims that Sri Lanka has the lowest petrol and diesel prices in the South Asian region—except for Pakistan, which has a lower diesel price. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/slide-1/Minister-Pathirana-correct-only-on-low-diesel-prices-in-Sri-Lanka/329-219516",
    "url_hash": "5bf6f8673757e6b94026f219254ab17b",
    "ut": 1630552112,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "South Asian",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Brunel International Lecture Series - South Asia lecture",
    "source": "ice.org.uk",
    "snippet": "Travelling virtually around the world, Seth Schultz will present his lecture alongside a regional panel of key industry thought leaders where they will debate some of the biggest issues facing the planet and the profession.",
    "url": "https://ice.org.uk/eventarchive/brunel-international-lecture-south-asia-webinar",
    "url_hash": "c3faaecbe3e4078afafd62e80ae18903",
    "ut": 1630552116,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Seth Schultz",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "PPP - to run or ruin sports in Sri Lanka?",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "While many Sri Lankans are celebrating the country's heroics in the Paralympics in Japan, little do they know about what appears to be a major power shift in sports management in the island. Public-Private Partnership,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/PPP-to-run-or-ruin-sports-in-Sri-Lanka/108-219509",
    "url_hash": "41a78adf640af767da110421d9b975d1",
    "ut": 1630552122,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankans",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Paralympics",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Japan",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Public-Private Partnership",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          40
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Nedungamuwe Raja leaves Kandy",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Nedungamuwe Raja the tusker that carried the casket of sacred relics in the final Randoli pageant in Kandy set off on its return journey las ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/main_image/Nedungamuwe-Raja-leaves-Kandy/346-219515",
    "url_hash": "6ebbfd3a4deadac23cbccb8fdeec9575",
    "ut": 1630552165,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nedungamuwe Raja",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Randoli",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Kandy",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "BoI registered company among those hoarding sugar",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "A company registered with the Board of Investment (BoI) was among a number of institutions found to be hoarding sugar yesterday, Daily Mirror learns. The warehouse of the company and a number of other places were raided yesterday aft .",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/front_page/BoI-registered-company-among-those-hoarding-sugar/238-219513",
    "url_hash": "1ca7062e14d5e6bf203b26b8a42572e7",
    "ut": 1630552165,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Board of Investment",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Daily Mirror",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          42
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "PPP - to run or ruin sports in Sri Lanka?",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "While many Sri Lankans are celebrating the country's heroics in the Paralympics in Japan, little do they know about what appears to be a major power shift in sports management in the island. Public-Private Partnership,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/PPP-to-run-or-ruin-sports-in-Sri-Lanka/342-219509",
    "url_hash": "701bcedd75fc4e346d94fdb7bd84c6eb",
    "ut": 1630552174,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankans",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Paralympics",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Japan",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Public-Private Partnership",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          40
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "CJ nominates Trial-at-Bar bench to hear Easter Sunday attacks trial",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Attorney General had filed 23,270 charges against 25 accused in connection with the Easter Sunday suicide bomb attacks took place on April 21, 2019 which killed 269 people ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/front_page/CJ-nominates-Trial-at-Bar-bench-to-hear-Easter-Sunday-attacks-trial/238-219512",
    "url_hash": "20c1d7a75d47671d0b9505c89158f55c",
    "ut": 1630552201,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "23,270",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "25",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Easter",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "April 21, 2019",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "269",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Govt. response to Easter Carnage: Vatican Ambassador meets FM",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Envoy suggests powwow with Catholic Bishops Conference Foreign Minister Prof. G.L. Peiris, on Tuesday (31), briefed His Eminence Archbishop Brian Udaigwe, Apostolic Nuncio (the Vatican Ambassador) to Sri Lanka,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/govt-response-to-easter-carnage-vatican-ambassador-meets-fm/",
    "url_hash": "2aa715c077cbae65331cc40f10693075",
    "ut": 1630552301,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Catholic Bishops Conference Foreign",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "G.L. Peiris",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Tuesday",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Brian Udaigwe",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Apostolic Nuncio",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Vatican",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka expecting 12 million more COVID vaccine doses",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "The SPC Chairman Dr. Prasanna Gunasena stated that a total of 08 million doses of the Sinopharm vaccine and 04 million doses of the Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine are scheduled to arrive on the island during this period. According to official data, Sri Lanka has ...",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news/76606/sri-lanka-expecting-12-million-more-covid-vaccine-doses",
    "url_hash": "e7c1c3f3624ef4432168e6603237ac05",
    "ut": 1630553491,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SPC",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Prasanna Gunasena",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "08 million",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sinopharm",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "04 million",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Pfizer",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          46
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "'I trust our team's strength' - Dasun Shanaka backs Sri Lanka's spinners to come good against South Africa",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "Captain feels they have the 'better spin-bowling contingent' than opponents South Africa ahead of the limited-overs series",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/i-trust-our-teams-strength-dasun-shanaka-backs-sri-lankas-spinners-to-come-good-against-south-africa/",
    "url_hash": "0e822481c862b1cfd7566884aac08d3b",
    "ut": 1630553491,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "South Africa",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "High-profile forum held to support Sri Lankan exporters of organic products",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Market access and export earnings More than 150 decision makers of European importers, retailers and wholesalers met and discussed virtually with certified Sri Lankan exporters of organic products in presence of the Secretary of the Ministry of Agriculture Prof.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/high-profile-forum-held-to-support-sri-lankan-exporters-of-organic-products/",
    "url_hash": "be34a38f749a4fbe4ad0a73ca187e062",
    "ut": 1630554391,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "More than 150",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "European",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Ministry of Agriculture",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka declares economic emergency",
    "source": "www.sentinelassam.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has declared an economic emergency, after a steep fall in the value of the South Asian country's currency caused a spike in food prices. Authorities say they will take control of",
    "url": "https://www.sentinelassam.com/international/sri-lanka-declares-economic-emergency-552945",
    "url_hash": "67f259459da9e869bf5ff9255eaad426",
    "ut": 1630555689,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "South Asian",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Cycle Pure Agarbathi becomes title sponsor of Sri Lanka Vs South Africa Series 2021",
    "source": "www.exchange4media.com",
    "snippet": "This association will reaffirm brand's commitment to cricket and to the Sri Lankan market, said Arjun Ranga, MD, Cycle Pure Agarbathi",
    "url": "https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/cycle-pure-agarbathi-becomes-title-sponsor-partner-for-sri-lanka-premier-league-2021-115384.html",
    "url_hash": "7b9580ca45429119c461111120499f16",
    "ut": 1630555939,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Arjun Ranga",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "MD",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "VIDEO: Elephant gives birth to twins for the first time in nearly 80 years",
    "source": "www.gulftoday.ae",
    "snippet": "Surangi, 25, at the Pinnawala Elephant Orphanage in Sri Lanka, gave birth to two healthy twins, according to officials of the institution.",
    "url": "https://www.gulftoday.ae/lifestyle/2021/09/01/elephant-gives-birth-to-twins-for-the-first-time-in-nearly-80-years",
    "url_hash": "9164dd4f2cc413a6334f44fb64022d08",
    "ut": 1630556289,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Surangi",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "25",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Pinnawala Elephant Orphanage",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Will Sri Lanka's tourism rise again with the new visa system? Arabiers Sri lanka explains",
    "source": "bizenglish.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "The Sri Lanka Tourism Development Authority's (SLTDA) new tourist mobile application provides a visa application facility for tourists. By applying through this app, tourists are able to obtain a 180-day visa for Sri Lanka.",
    "url": "http://bizenglish.adaderana.lk/will-sri-lankas-tourism-rise-again-with-the-new-visa-system-arabiers-sri-lanka-explains/",
    "url_hash": "340ff72f365a9048684c8dd17eb4e803",
    "ut": 1630558214,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Sri Lanka Tourism Development Authority's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "180-day",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          37
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Manning Market turns busy",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "New Peliyagoda Manning Market was open today enabling farmers to sell their produce conveniently under one roof. Vendors are seen piling large stocks of vegetables to sell them on wholesale. Pix by Nimalsiri Edirisinghe .",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Manning-Market-turns-busy/342-219532",
    "url_hash": "f630ae91e59a8ca9022d121b80b40baf",
    "ut": 1630559282,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "one",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nimalsiri Edirisinghe",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Coastal belt in India's Ernakulam on high alert for Sri Lankans",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The long coastline in the district has been on high alert for the past 72 hours following intelligence input that some Sri Lankan nationals will try to start their voyage to Pakistan from one of the harbours in Ernakulam and Alappuzha.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Coastal-belt-in-Indias-Ernakulam-on-high-alert-for-Sri-Lankans/108-219521",
    "url_hash": "cce3436dd861ba1fca05e76eeeba1554",
    "ut": 1630559336,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "the past 72 hours",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "one",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ernakulam",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Alappuzha",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Cash rewards for Tokyo Paralympic medal winners",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Tokyo Paralympic Games medal winners Dinesh Priyantha Herath and Samitha Dulan are set to receive a huge cash prize from the Sports Ministry once they arrive on 7. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Cash-rewards-for-Tokyo-Paralympic-medal-winners/108-219522",
    "url_hash": "48e951a7936324cf487153a595a4871f",
    "ut": 1630559336,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Tokyo",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Paralympic Games",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Priyantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Samitha Dulan",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sports Ministry",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "7",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Planning an International Trip? 10 Countries That Are Now Open For Indian Travellers: UAE, Sri Lanka & More",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "India was among the worst-hit countries around the world in the wake of the deadly second wave of the coronavirus. However, with the vaccination drive gaining momentum in the country, the situation is easing up gradually.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-in/autos/news/planning-an-international-trip-10-countries-that-are-now-open-for-indian-travellers/ar-AAO0gom",
    "url_hash": "193e0f951a65006ec3e6f74086a32fbd",
    "ut": 1630559346,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "second",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Dasun Shanaka reveals Team Combinaton : Sri Lanka's Probable playing 11 for the 1st ODI Between SL and SA and why?",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "There was a Pre match Press conference held yesterday, There Shanaka revealed His team combination : 3 Spinners, 2 Fast bowlers and 6 Batsman, It was also revealed that Kusal perera, Will not play, So",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/blogs/dasun-shanaka-reveals-team-combinaton-sri-lankas-probable-playing-11-for-the-1st-odi-between-sl-and-sa-and-why/",
    "url_hash": "6f3938cefe3d4b9f2dbb30c1b9f614bf",
    "ut": 1630559346,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "3",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "2",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kusal",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Elpitiya Plantations launches locally harvested 'BerryMuch' fresh berries",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Fresh berries lovingly nurtured in Sri Lanka under the brand name, 'BerryMuch' will be launched in Sri Lanka. Harvested in the salubrious environs of Elpitiya Plantations PLC, the leading plantations company brings the fresh goodness of 'BerryMuch' to all Sri Lankans.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/press-releases/Elpitiya-Plantations-launches-locally-harvested-BerryMuch-fresh-berries/335-219523",
    "url_hash": "fc4fe971a0464a421b57689977383036",
    "ut": 1630559365,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Elpitiya Plantations PLC",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankans",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          48
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "S&T Interiors awarded Rs 1.94 billion Hilton Colombo refurbishment",
    "source": "colombogazette.com",
    "snippet": "Hilton Hotels Corporation is recognized internationally as a preeminent hospitality company, where in Sri Lanka the Hilton Colombo is known as a pioneer of the hospitality industry. The interior upgrade by equally renowned S&T Interiors is expected to ...",
    "url": "https://colombogazette.com/2021/09/02/st-interiors-awarded-rs-1-94-billion-hilton-colombo-refurbishment/",
    "url_hash": "4947a9071d63a6fcf74c3caf92c8cc17",
    "ut": 1630559407,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Hilton Hotels Corporation",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Hilton Colombo",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "S&T Interiors",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sugar & Rice Control Price Gazette to be issued on Thursday (02)",
    "source": "www.newsfirst.lk",
    "snippet": "The State Ministry of Consumer Protection says that a gazette notification will be issued today (02) to impose a control price for - Get the latest breaking news and top stories from Sri Lanka, the latest political news,",
    "url": "https://www.newsfirst.lk/2021/09/02/sugar-rice-control-price-gazette-to-be-issued-on-thursday-02/",
    "url_hash": "f4f344a12dd1a3b8be8d06e66d2a20ec",
    "ut": 1630559827,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The State Ministry of Consumer Protection",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "02",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lankan SEP celebrates Wije Dias's 80th birthday",
    "source": "www.wsws.org",
    "snippet": "ICFI leaders and SEP members hail the Trotskyist veteran's decades of struggle for socialist internationalism.",
    "url": "https://www.wsws.org/en/articles/2021/09/02/wije-s02.html",
    "url_hash": "66c62c8249b3b68998b8e65c2b161b72",
    "ut": 1630560611,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SEP",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Trotskyist",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "decades",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "IYSSE (Sri Lanka) to hold online meeting on US debacle in Afghanistan",
    "source": "www.wsws.org",
    "snippet": "The US invasion of Afghanistan was part of Washington's attempts to strengthen its position against its main rivals—China and Russia—and the European imperialist powers, its supposed allies.",
    "url": "https://www.wsws.org/en/articles/2021/09/02/slyi-s02.html",
    "url_hash": "f866c121ad07c00183653b66f38e8284",
    "ut": 1630560762,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Afghanistan",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Washington",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "China",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "European",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Claims over a food shortage in the country refuted",
    "source": "www.hirunews.lk",
    "snippet": "While many international news outlets have reported regarding the declaration of economic emergency in Sri Lanka following a significant fall in the Sri Lankan rupee and the hike in food prices, State Minister of Money & Capital Market and State Enterprise Reforms,",
    "url": "https://www.hirunews.lk/english/281177/claims-over-a-food-shortage-in-the-country-refuted",
    "url_hash": "4bdc42d16f49d58f6f7d20026c5bfa45",
    "ut": 1630561251,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "State",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Money & Capital Market",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Decision on quarantine curfew tomorrow: Army Chief",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Presidential Task Force on COVID-19 headed by President Gotabaya Rajapaksa will meet tomorrow morning to take a decision whether the quarantine curfew imposed in the country will be further extended or lifted after Monday,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Decision-on-quarantine-curfew-tomorrow-Army-Chief/108-219524",
    "url_hash": "271dea068f9b123e5cecf5684a2db179",
    "ut": 1630562936,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Presidential Task Force",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gotabaya Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "tomorrow",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "morning",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Monday",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "High Commissioner of Sri Lanka to Kenya Kananathan visits Hela Clothing factory in Kenya",
    "source": "bizenglish.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "As part of the economic diplomacy programme of the High Commission, the High Commissioner of Sri Lanka to Kenya Velupillai Kananathan, visited on 31 August, 2021 the Hela Clothing factory in Nairobi.",
    "url": "http://bizenglish.adaderana.lk/high-commissioner-of-sri-lanka-to-kenya-kananathan-visits-hela-clothing-factory-in-kenya/",
    "url_hash": "b53b98e6d56a8a93a4ddd701714137be",
    "ut": 1630562951,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the High Commission",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Kenya",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Velupillai Kananathan",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "31 August",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2021",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Nairobi",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Claims over a food shortage in the country refuted",
    "source": "www.hirunews.lk",
    "snippet": "While many international news outlets have reported regarding the declaration of economic emergency in Sri Lanka following a significant fall in the Sri Lankan rupee and the hike in food prices, State Minister of Money & Capital Market and State Enterprise Reforms,",
    "url": "https://www.hirunews.lk/goldfmnews/281177/claims-over-a-food-shortage-in-the-country-refuted",
    "url_hash": "b572c7423e2867db20246534eb0dee48",
    "ut": 1630562956,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "State",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Money & Capital Market",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Ascentic receives quadruple recognition as Best Workplace for 2021",
    "source": "colombogazette.com",
    "snippet": "Ascentic, a leading software development company based in Sri Lanka with offices in Sweden and a track-record of exponential growth in the recent months, was recently ranked at number 43 in the Best W",
    "url": "https://colombogazette.com/2021/09/02/ascentic-receives-quadruple-recognition-as-best-workplace-for-2021/",
    "url_hash": "a93be34aee9da522674209cdf5b554b2",
    "ut": 1630563690,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sweden",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the recent months",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "number 43",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Multiple services declared as Essential Services",
    "source": "www.newsfirst.lk",
    "snippet": "President has declared several services as essential services under the Essential Public Services Act. As per the Gazette Notification - Get the latest breaking news and top stories from Sri Lanka, the latest political news,",
    "url": "https://www.newsfirst.lk/2021/09/02/multiple-services-declared-as-essential-services/",
    "url_hash": "10b9fda9b12e217387de180b932aea17",
    "ut": 1630565010,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Essential Public Services Act",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Gazette Notification - Get",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "SLT-MOBITEL Supports Smart Building Technologies for One Galle Face Mall and One Galle Face Tower",
    "source": "bizenglish.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "One Galle Face Tower is an international grade business premises, providing over 530,000 sq.ft of premium office space and world ... Vice President (Operations) of Shangri-La Group, Sri Lanka, Mr. Timothy Wright gave his comments, saying, \"We are ...",
    "url": "http://bizenglish.adaderana.lk/slt-mobitel-supports-smart-building-technologies-for-one-galle-face-mall-and-one-galle-face-tower/",
    "url_hash": "d8b4664273385c5544f516d405b0ac58",
    "ut": 1630565600,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "One",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Galle Face Tower",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "over 530,000",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Shangri-La Group",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          35
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Timothy Wright",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "CID probes couple involved in pornographic video at Pahanthudawa waterfall",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Criminal Investigations Department (CID) has launched an investigation into a incident in which a teenage couple were involved in a pornographic video at the Pahanthudawa waterfall in Balangoda, which is now widely circulated on social media.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/front_page/CID-probes-couple-involved-in-pornographic-video-at-Pahanthudawa-waterfall/238-219514",
    "url_hash": "a78c1a2ee18d26d78ce2d59dac6ce73d",
    "ut": 1630566356,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Criminal Investigations Department",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Pahanthudawa",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Balangoda",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Bus operations in provinces after COVID committee decision tomorrow: Dilum",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Though the inter provincial bus services are suspended, transport within the provinces could be resumed following the decision taken by the COVID-19 committee tomorrow, Transport State Minister Dilum Amunugama said.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Bus-operations-in-provinces-after-COVID-committee-decision-tomorrow-Dilum/108-219527",
    "url_hash": "5aa71e91677aeb8c5c9c66538c2ed03e",
    "ut": 1630566479,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the COVID-19 committee",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "tomorrow",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Dilum Amunugama",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Bus operations in provinces after COVID committee decision tomorrow: Dilum",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Though the inter-provincial transport bus services are suspended, transport within the provinces could be resumed following the decision taken by the COVID-19 committee tomorrow, Transport State Minister Dilum Amunugama said.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Bus-operations-in-provinces-after-COVID-committee-decision-tomorrow-Dilum/342-219527",
    "url_hash": "501295703d459552365ca69024aa3d06",
    "ut": 1630566505,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the COVID-19 committee",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "tomorrow",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Dilum Amunugama",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "No internal investigation on two former Jt. COOs of Asia Capital, says Director",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Responding to recent media reports regarding two former Joint Chief Operating Officers Reyhan Morris and Sandun Hettige of Asia Capital PLC, a top official of the company said there was no internal investigation carried out on the conduct or actions of the two individuals during their tenure at Asia Capital group.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business_247/No-internal-investigation-on-two-former-Jt-COOs-of-Asia-Capital-says-Director/395-219525",
    "url_hash": "1aba12698851d3ced12d7b5fa4842647",
    "ut": 1630566505,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Reyhan Morris",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sandun Hettige",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Asia Capital PLC",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Asia Capital",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          51
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka seizes staple stocks to rein in prices; says no food shortage",
    "source": "www.thepeninsulaqatar.com",
    "snippet": "Colombo: Sri Lanka's government has started seizing stocks of sugar and ... But since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic the island nation has put restrictions on imports of most non-essentials and also on some agricultural items to reduce spending ...",
    "url": "https://www.thepeninsulaqatar.com/article/02/09/2021/Sri-Lanka-seizes-staple-stocks-to-rein-in-prices-says-no-food-shortage",
    "url_hash": "e23c84744dcc094067c33d2d0d6063ed",
    "ut": 1630566516,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          5
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka denies reports of food shortage but declining forex, GDP drives inflation in pandemic-hit nation",
    "source": "www.firstpost.com",
    "snippet": "Since 2012, the Sri Lankan GDP growth rate has plummeted continuously and the manufacturing output has also not seen any growth, maintaining a flatline. It was amid these fragile conditions that the p",
    "url": "https://www.firstpost.com/world/sri-lanka-denies-reports-of-food-shortage-but-declining-forex-gdp-drives-inflation-in-pandemic-hit-nation-9931621.html",
    "url_hash": "e39e19a10296c73b055b1d6da0f18b29",
    "ut": 1630568494,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2012",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka faces no food shortage: Govt.",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The government today said the country is not facing any food shortages at present and the reduced access to essential commodities are due to traders hoarding stocks. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business/Sri-Lanka-faces-no-food-shortage-Govt/215-219526",
    "url_hash": "4ef4e124af49d64d8a11695e248ed81f",
    "ut": 1630570075,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          3
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Daily Mirror Sportsline | Shehan Daniel speaks to former cricketer Russel Arnold",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Mirror Sportsline | Shehan Daniel speaks to former cricketer Russel Arnold ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/ipad-video/Daily-Mirror-Sportsline-Shehan-Daniel-speaks-to-former-cricketer-Russel-Arnold/168-219528",
    "url_hash": "8351f6f61655c25b2f6ce0b4a05300cb",
    "ut": 1630570075,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Shehan Daniel",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Russel Arnold",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Prepare, publish plans on how transportation function after re-opening country: Dr. Herath",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Before opening the country, plans should be submitted to launch a formal public service, Health Services Deputy Director General Dr. Hemantha Herath said. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Prepare-publish-plans-on-how-transportation-function-after-re-opening-country-Dr-Herath/108-219529",
    "url_hash": "f6c617b8f8a9d807d342ed6bbe5b747f",
    "ut": 1630570085,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Health Services",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hemantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Police act to protect health authorities in Weligama",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Responding to a video being circulated on social media in which a police officer was seen using his baton on Weligama residents during a vaccination programme on Wednesday, the police said they had to remove the residents to prevent health authorities from being attacked.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/top_story/Police-act-to-protect-health-authorities-in-Weligama/155-219530",
    "url_hash": "50fcf97efc0fa84df422016a81525008",
    "ut": 1630570085,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Weligama",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Daily Mirror Sportsline | Shehan Daniel speaks to former cricketer Russel Arnold",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Mirror Sportsline | Shehan Daniel speaks to former cricketer Russel Arnold ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/news-video/Daily-Mirror-Sportsline-Shehan-Daniel-speaks-to-former-cricketer-Russel-Arnold/196-219528",
    "url_hash": "cf64a24e032ee3e1e324e97606b04543",
    "ut": 1630570085,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Shehan Daniel",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Russel Arnold",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Organize public transportation before re-opening country: Dr. Herath",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Before re-opening the country, plans should be submitted to organize how public transportation would operate, Health Services Deputy Director General Dr. Hemantha Herath said. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Organize-public-transportation-before-re-opening-country-Dr-Herath/108-219529",
    "url_hash": "d84e2fadfa7e36228a0c52b232fad8ab",
    "ut": 1630570087,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Health Services",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hemantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka seizes sugar, rice stocks as food shortages bite",
    "source": "www.freemalaysiatoday.com",
    "snippet": "COLOMBO: Sri Lanka's government has started seizing stocks of sugar and rice from warehouses and will release them on the open market at regulated prices from Thursday as part of emergency measures to stop hoarding,",
    "url": "https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/world/2021/09/02/sri-lanka-seizes-sugar-rice-stocks-as-food-shortages-bite/",
    "url_hash": "d6f6a4c60f7f71d0d1bb0e1a34085d36",
    "ut": 1630570093,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Thursday",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Police act to protect health authorities in Weligama",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Responding to a video being circulated on social media in which a police officer was seen using his baton on Weligama residents during a vaccination programme on Wednesday, the police said they had to remove the residents to prevent health authorities from ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Police-act-to-protect-health-authorities-in-Weligama/108-219530",
    "url_hash": "74359c5ec40fc7bfc07ed6a74cfbc2cc",
    "ut": 1630570093,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Weligama",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "WHO launches hub in Berlin to help prevent future pandemics",
    "source": "www.thepeninsulaqatar.com",
    "snippet": "China has responded to continuing speculation about a leak from the Wuhan Institute of Virology by suggesting the virus could have escaped from Fort Detrick ... GQ Men Of The Year Awards on Wednesday. Sri Lanka's government has started seizing stocks ...",
    "url": "https://www.thepeninsulaqatar.com/article/02/09/2021/WHO-launches-hub-in-Berlin-to-help-prevent-future-pandemics",
    "url_hash": "0afa69abd0d2e3bca6c1c42d6ec835fb",
    "ut": 1630570105,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "China",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Wuhan Institute of Virology",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Fort Detrick",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka declares economic emergency",
    "source": "newstodaynet.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has declared an economic emergency, after a steep fall in the value of the South Asian country's currency caused a spike in food prices. Continue Reading →",
    "url": "https://newstodaynet.com/index.php/2021/09/02/sri-lanka-declares-economic-emergency/",
    "url_hash": "5734ac3db6eb65fc28d36b66f0913266",
    "ut": 1630570116,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "South Asian",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Prepare, publish plans on how transportation function after re-opening country: Dr. Herath",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Before opening the country, plans should be submitted to launch a formal public service, Health Services Deputy Director General Dr. Hemantha Herath said. Addressing the media today, he said if proper plans for public service are not announced, the ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Prepare-publish-plans-on-how-transportation-shod-work-after-re-opening-the-country-Dr-Herath/342-219529",
    "url_hash": "fe0d54cc9ae705d11b24f829e08ed81b",
    "ut": 1630570121,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Health Services",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hemantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka denies reports of food shortage but declining forex, GDP drives inflation in pandemic-hit nation",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's economy is suffering through an unprecedented slump in the wake of the COVID-19 pandemic, which may have triggered a food crisis as well.Over the past week, various media reports claimed that country was staring at an acute food shortage resulting from a combination of factors,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/sri-lanka-denies-reports-of-food-shortage-but-declining-forex-gdp-drives-inflation-in-pandemic-hit-nation/ar-AAO0REU",
    "url_hash": "9e360bfc94260524a68a82b3532b4818",
    "ut": 1630570143,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the past week",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Organize public transportation before re-opening country: Dr. Herath",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Before re-opening the country, plans should be submitted to organize how public transportation would operate, Health Services Deputy Director General Dr. Hemantha Herath said. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Organize-public-transportation-before-re-opening-country-Dr-Herath/342-219529",
    "url_hash": "2d5e2e5a50bfa9f5100adfe58671a35b",
    "ut": 1630570240,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Health Services",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hemantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Covid: Sri Lanka in economic emergency as food prices soar",
    "source": "www.businessghana.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has declared an economic emergency, after a steep fall in the value of the South Asian country's currency caused a spike in",
    "url": "https://www.businessghana.com/site/news/politics/245595/Covid-Sri-Lanka-in-economic-emergency-as-food-prices-soar",
    "url_hash": "8033eaa0cf16a790978b2f8752fea77c",
    "ut": 1630570776,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "South Asian",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lankan drug seizure accused aimed for LTTE revival - NIA",
    "source": "www.dailynews.lk",
    "snippet": "Suspecting that the accused in the recent Sri Lankan arms and drugs seizure case were aiding the revival of the activities of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam (LTTE) in Sri Lanka, the National Investigation Agency (NIA) has moved a Special Court for invoking the Unlawful Activities Prevention Act (UAPA) against them.",
    "url": "http://www.dailynews.lk/2021/09/02/world/258284/sri-lankan-drug-seizure-accused-aimed-ltte-revival-nia",
    "url_hash": "c420d4ce1c3bb03e660ee5c1d94b942b",
    "ut": 1630573531,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "LTTE",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the National Investigation Agency",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          39
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Special Court",
        "start_end": [
          45,
          47
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LAW",
        "text": "the Unlawful Activities Prevention Act",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          54
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "United States to support conservation of historical Kandy monuments",
    "source": "www.lankabusinessonline.com",
    "snippet": "The United States government, through the U.S. Ambassadors Fund for Cultural Preservation (AFCP), has awarded a grant to conserve a 17th century Royal Palace and Archaeology Museum in Kandy. Funding for the project totals over 52 million Sri Lankan rupees ($265,",
    "url": "https://www.lankabusinessonline.com/united-states-to-support-conservation-of-historical-kandy-monuments/",
    "url_hash": "0e1e622499e4d4aaa3fe43850c4e1019",
    "ut": 1630573705,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "United States",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the U.S. Ambassadors Fund for Cultural Preservation",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "17th century",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Royal Palace",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Archaeology Museum",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kandy",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "265",
        "start_end": [
          47,
          48
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Get the stones of uneasy topics rolling",
    "source": "www.newindianexpress.com",
    "snippet": "Then came a remix that dropped his name entirely, and most recently, a Rolling Stone India cover featuring only Dhee and Shan Vincent de Paul (both of whom rose to fame through collaborations with Arivu).",
    "url": "https://www.newindianexpress.com/opinions/2021/sep/02/get-the-stones-of-uneasy-topics-rolling-2352988.html",
    "url_hash": "1e26615ea0fd8948a43ea6d641a450b5",
    "ut": 1630573705,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "a Rolling Stone India",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Dhee",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Shan Vincent de Paul",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Arivu",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Aiden Markram, Kagiso Rabada back for Proteas for opening ODi against Sri Lanka",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lankan captain Dasun Chanaka won the toss and chose to bat in the opening One-Day International against South Africa.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-za/sport/cricket/aiden-markram-kagiso-rabada-back-for-proteas-for-opening-odi-against-sri-lanka/ar-AAO0ZtN",
    "url_hash": "9618c57c247112791fbd52ed8ee087c4",
    "ut": 1630573717,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Dasun Chanaka",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "One-Day",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "South Africa",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "U.S. to support conservation of historical Kandy monuments",
    "source": "www.srilankaguardian.org",
    "snippet": "The United States government, through the U.S. Ambassadors Fund for Cultural Preservation (AFCP), has awarded a grant to conserve a 17th century Royal Palace and Archaeology Museum in Kandy. Funding for the project totals over 52 million Sri Lankan rupees ($265,",
    "url": "http://www.srilankaguardian.org/2021/09/us-to-support-conservation-of.html",
    "url_hash": "456374e094eacc575b91126fbdb23fe9",
    "ut": 1630573885,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "United States",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the U.S. Ambassadors Fund for Cultural Preservation",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "17th century",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Royal Palace",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Archaeology Museum",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kandy",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "265",
        "start_end": [
          47,
          48
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka Declares Economic Emergency To Contain Inflation. Know Reasons Behind Skyrocketing Food Prices",
    "source": "news.abplive.com",
    "snippet": "One of the reasons behind rising prices of many essential items over the last 12 months, according to the Sri Lanka's department of Census and Statistics, as per Reuters.",
    "url": "https://news.abplive.com/news/world/sri-lanka-declares-economic-emergency-to-contain-inflation-know-reasons-behind-skyrocketing-food-prices-1479805",
    "url_hash": "77b8fb5691ee3d6a982bd41071858a00",
    "ut": 1630573993,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "One",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the last 12 months",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Reuters",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Rs. 52 Mn from US to conserve 17th century Royal Palace in Kandy",
    "source": "www.newsfirst.lk",
    "snippet": "The United States government, through the U.S. Ambassadors Fund for Cultural Preservation (AFCP), has awarded a grant to conserve a - Get the latest breaking news and top stories from Sri Lanka, the latest political news,",
    "url": "https://www.newsfirst.lk/2021/09/02/rs-52-mn-from-us-to-conserve-17th-century-royal-palace-in-kandy/",
    "url_hash": "434cbca5d53a5f08261610cda85e8eb3",
    "ut": 1630576105,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "United States",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the U.S. Ambassadors Fund for Cultural Preservation",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Daily Mirror Sportsline | Shehan Daniel speaks to former cricketer Russel Arnold",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Comments will be edited (grammar, spelling and slang) and authorized at the discretion of Daily Mirror online. The website also has the right not to publish selected comments.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/news-video/Daily-Mirror-Sportsline-Shehan-Daniel-speaks-to-former-cricketer-Russel-Arnold/251-219528",
    "url_hash": "b904a9fa105a4d84a06a898b640f7a93",
    "ut": 1630577279,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Daily Mirror",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Asia Capital says no internal investigations on two former Jt. COOs",
    "source": "www.ft.lk",
    "snippet": "Asia Capital Plc in a statement said yesterday that there are no internal investigations on the two former Joint Chief Operating Officers (COOs) Reyhan Morris and Sandun Hettige over their conduct or actions during their tenure in the Company .",
    "url": "https://www.ft.lk/business/Asia-Capital-says-no-internal-investigations-on-two-former-Jt-COOs/34-722547",
    "url_hash": "b5e41fba2c91e4c2b7d093d59f5fd2e8",
    "ut": 1630577293,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Asia Capital Plc",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Reyhan Morris",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sandun Hettige",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Company",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Maximum retail price set for oximeter",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "A maximum retail price of Rs 3000 has been declared for a Pulse Oximeter, State Minister Prof. Channa Jayasumana said. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Maximum-retail-price-set-for-oximeter/108-219534",
    "url_hash": "f334230660abb649a9bb1175642475e5",
    "ut": 1630577321,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "a Pulse Oximeter",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "State",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Channa Jayasumana",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Jailors found mobile phone in Rishad Bathiudeen's possession",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The prisons officers found a mobile phone in the possession of former Minister Rishad Bathiudeen who is currently in remand custody at the Magazine Prison. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Jailors-found-mobile-phone-in-Rishad-Bathiudeens-possession/108-219533",
    "url_hash": "eed742a2d3480dbad0073ef5dd89df8b",
    "ut": 1630577321,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Rishad Bathiudeen",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Magazine Prison",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "Sri Lanka 10-year old's parakeet shot flies high in UK Wildlife Photographer Awards",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "A photograph of a parakeet feeding three chicks peeking out of a nest holeshot by a 10-year old in Sri Lanka during the Covid-19 lockdown has been highly commended in the UK Wildlife Photographer Awards 2021.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-10-year-olds-parakeet-shot-flies-high-in-uk-wildlife-photographer-awards-85712/",
    "url_hash": "46a6c5d953b2946f19001e05437705c2",
    "ut": 1630577331,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "three",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "10-year old",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          23
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-02",
    "title": "China influencing world using army of fake social media accounts, but why?",
    "source": "www.canindia.com",
    "snippet": "The Chinese Ambassador to Sri Lanka, Qi Zhenhong, at a recent meeting with Health Minister Pavithra Wanniarachchi (now appointed as the Minister of",
    "url": "https://www.canindia.com/china-influencing-world-using-army-of-fake-social-media-accounts-but-why/",
    "url_hash": "2075a5b9921760090d4d15c4538a6780",
    "ut": 1630577958,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Chinese",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
