[
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka to launch massive tourism campaign in Russia and Ukraine",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The Sri Lankan Government will launch a massive tourism campaign in Russia and Ukraine in order to attract more tourists to visit the island nation. Several programmes as part of the tourism promotional campaign will be conducted in Russia and Ukraine under the patronage of Tourism Minister Prasanna Ranatunga,",
    "url": "http://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/sri-lanka-to-launch-massive-tourism-campaign-in-russia-and-ukraine/ar-AAOagDc",
    "url_hash": "4d7357f47d1192053c0d5fdc66aaf0e1",
    "ut": 1630973285,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Sri Lankan Government",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          40
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Prasanna Ranatunga",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka should stop printing money, get IMF help; price controls a useless drama: legislator",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka should stop money printing and go to the International Monetary Fund to fix monetary policy instead of invoking emergency laws to control food prices, which will create black markets, opposition legislator Rauff Hakeem said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-should-stop-printing-money-get-imf-help-price-controls-a-useless-drama-legislator-85846/",
    "url_hash": "13a0e61da8e3f34158f7a8a4e616ed5f",
    "ut": 1630973699,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Rauff Hakeem",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka should stop printing money, get IMF help; emergency, price controls useless: Hakeem",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka should stop money printing and go to the International Monetary Fund to fix monetary policy instead of invoking emergency laws to control food prices, which will create black markets, opposition legislator Rauff Hakeem said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-should-stop-printing-money-get-imf-help-emergency-price-controls-useless-hakeem-85846/",
    "url_hash": "d43c2c47364e8208f497197bd9f652a8",
    "ut": 1630973699,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Rauff Hakeem",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka to launch massive tourism campaign in Russia and Ukraine",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The Sri Lankan Government will launch a massive tourism campaign in Russia and Ukraine in order to attract more tourists to visit the island nation. Several programmes as part of the tourism promotional campaign will be conducted in Russia and Ukraine under the patronage of Tourism Minister Prasanna Ranatunga,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/sri-lanka-to-launch-massive-tourism-campaign-in-russia-and-ukraine/ar-AAOagDc",
    "url_hash": "92b7abf7c0808e7ecc110dac5a5e3d20",
    "ut": 1630974402,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Sri Lankan Government",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          40
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Prasanna Ranatunga",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "SL's anti vaxxers cause alarm for medical workers",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "People urged not to have any preference to one specific vaccine and to take what is available People, especially those above 60 years who face genuine reasons for not being vaccinated yet, urged to contact medical experts .",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/SLs-anti-vaxxers-cause-alarm-for-medical-workers/342-219863",
    "url_hash": "d04fb5bf8885f24ce363936cebb07c5c",
    "ut": 1630976875,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "one",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "60 years",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "SL's anti vaxxers cause alarm for medical workers",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "People urged not to have any preference to one specific vaccine and to take what is available People, especially those above 60 years who face genuine reasons for not being vaccinated yet, urged to contact medical experts .",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/SLs-anti-vaxxers-cause-alarm-for-medical-workers/108-219863",
    "url_hash": "faa3daef388ea94789efe87001e36296",
    "ut": 1630976890,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "one",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "60 years",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Red Carpet welcome awaits Sri Lankan Paralympics Team",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's Paralympic Gold Medallist Dinesh Priyantha Herath and Bronze Medallist Samitha Dulan along with the rest of the team members will receive a red carpet welcome when they arrive in the island today after competing in the 16th Tokyo Para Games ...",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/red-carpet-welcome-awaits-sri-lankan-paralympics-team/ar-AAOagD4",
    "url_hash": "f0007a214a5e538309c6644502f1c438",
    "ut": 1630977162,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Paralympic Gold Medallist Dinesh Priyantha Herath",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Bronze Medallist Samitha Dulan",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "16th",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          40
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "EVENT",
        "text": "Tokyo Para Games",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          43
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Experts urge those who recover from COVID to avoid strenuous work for a few weeks",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Patients who have recovered from COVID-19 have been advised not to over-exert and do strenuous exercises They just need to be careful for a few weeks before they can return back to their normal lives,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Experts-urge-those-who-recover-from-COVID-to-avoid-strenuous-work-for-a-few-weeks/342-219862",
    "url_hash": "f5342d1b7984f9c1a4367128ba356160",
    "ut": 1630980475,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "a few weeks",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Experts urge those who recover from COVID to avoid strenuous work for a few weeks",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Patients who have recovered from COVID-19 have been advised not to over-exert and do strenuous exercises They just need to be careful for a few weeks before they can return back to their normal lives,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/top_story/Experts-urge-those-who-recover-from-COVID-to-avoid-strenuous-work-for-a-few-weeks/155-219862",
    "url_hash": "ff401df3f9652420b331a16a27e3dbd4",
    "ut": 1630980478,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "a few weeks",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Bridging the Gaps: The COVID-19 crisis and Sri Lanka's healthcare response",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "By Priyanka Jayawardena Like many other countries, Sri Lanka faces numerous challenges in the battle against COVID-19. The pandemic has caused deep uncertainty and presented a colossal challenge for the country's healthcare system.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/bridging-the-gaps-the-covid-19-crisis-and-sri-lankas-healthcare-response/",
    "url_hash": "6dc77ce7aa3224a38018bda6ff4a7a4f",
    "ut": 1630981327,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Priyanka Jayawardena Like",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Parakrama Samudraya, 1978 flood, and strength of tank bund",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "By Palitha Manchanayake Former Irrigation Engineer, Sri Lanka and Hydrologist/Flood Forecaster to the Commonwealth Bureau of Meteorology, Sydney, Australia In this article, the author wishes to highlight his experience during the November 1978 cyclone,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/parakrama-samudraya-1978-flood-and-strength-of-tank-bund/",
    "url_hash": "752e4840ce07f5f72896736eb00c51a5",
    "ut": 1630982362,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Palitha Manchanayake",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Hydrologist/Flood Forecaster",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Commonwealth Bureau of Meteorology",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sydney",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Australia",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "November 1978",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Be ruthless in the basics, Arthur implores",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "After a close 14-run win in the series-opener last Thurday, Sri Lanka were comfortably beaten in the rain-shortened second ODI on Sunday, losing by 67 runs on the Duckworth/Lewis method. That was after South Africa had chalked up an imposing total of 283 for 6 in 47 overs,",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/be-ruthless-in-the-basics-arthur-implores/",
    "url_hash": "babb879b2e890225fe100ba4827a2651",
    "ut": 1630983127,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "14",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "last Thurday",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "second",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "ODI",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "67",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "South Africa",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          46
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "283",
        "start_end": [
          53,
          54
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "6",
        "start_end": [
          55,
          56
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "47",
        "start_end": [
          57,
          58
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Customs approve Rs. 46.43Bn exports, netted Rs.9.34bn revenue during quarantine curfew: Spokesman",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Customs has approved exports valued at Rs.46.43 billion and collected import taxes amounting to Rs. 9.34 billion during the quarantine curfew period, Customs Media Spokesman and Deputy Director Sudattha Silva said.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Customs-approve-Rs-46-43Bn-exports-netted-Rs-9-34bn-revenue-during-quarantine-curfew-Spokesman/342-219864",
    "url_hash": "94fde2608ed48c7944ef554219d14749",
    "ut": 1630984075,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Customs",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "Rs.46.43 billion",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "9.34 billion",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Customs Media Spokesman",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sudattha Silva",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Customs approve Rs. 46.43Bn exports, netted Rs.9.34bn revenue during quarantine curfew: Spokesman",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Customs has approved exports valued at Rs.46.43 billion and collected import taxes amounting to Rs. 9.34 billion during the quarantine curfew period, Customs Media Spokesman and Deputy Director Sudattha Silva said.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Customs-approve-Rs-46-43Bn-exports-netted-Rs-9-34bn-revenue-during-quarantine-curfew-Spokesman/108-219864",
    "url_hash": "e30749ac078038b85ff4e2dc06dcc34e",
    "ut": 1630984093,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Customs",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "Rs.46.43 billion",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "9.34 billion",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Customs Media Spokesman",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sudattha Silva",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "COVID vaccine clinics operated by Army, Health Ministry today",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "COVID vaccination programmes conducted by the Ministry of Health and the Sri Lanka Army are continuing in many parts of the island today ( 07)",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news.php?nid=76721",
    "url_hash": "590e189de06f02e162f1c6ac102c8de0",
    "ut": 1630984099,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Ministry of Health",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sri Lanka Army",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "07",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka's fastest growing rural lender on the next phase of village regeneration",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's banks, even the state-owned ones ... SDF operates 51 branches and service centres in the island, many of them outside the Western Province. Through partnerships with Sarvodaya Shramadana Societies (SSS) at the village level, SDF is capable ...",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/brand_voice/sri-lankas-fastest-growing-rural-lender-on-the-next-phase-of-village-regeneration/",
    "url_hash": "e2f191682df216aa30d9a6ce4c678c13",
    "ut": 1630986859,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SDF",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "51",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Western Province",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SSS",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SDF",
        "start_end": [
          45,
          46
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Cabraal to step down as MP to take over Central Bank",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "State Minister of Money and Capital Markets, and State Enterprise Reforms, Ajith Nivard Cabraal is to step down from his portfolio and resign as a member of parliament to be sworn in as the Governor of the Central Bank.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Cabraal-to-step-down-as-MP-to-take-over-Central-Bank/108-219866",
    "url_hash": "a3d0fdd66d3750180e51217d700f209b",
    "ut": 1630987693,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Money and Capital Markets",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nivard Cabraal",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Central Bank",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Steps adopted to operate transport services during health risk: Dilum",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Three steps have been introduced and informed the health authorities by the Transport Ministry to operate the transport service when there is a health risk, Transport State Minister Dilum Amunugama said.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Steps-adopted-to-operate-transport-services-during-health-risk-Dilum/108-219865",
    "url_hash": "ba4b8afec696d6138be5cfe66c5fe727",
    "ut": 1630987693,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "Three",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Transport Ministry",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Dilum Amunugama",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Steps adopted to operate transport services during health risk: Dilum",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Three steps have been introduced and informed the health authorities by the Transport Ministry to operate the transport service when there is a health risk, Transport State Minister Dilum Amunugama said.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Steps-adopted-to-operate-transport-services-during-health-risk-Dilum/342-219865",
    "url_hash": "4e1fcc8023feaad3903d8712b2b201c9",
    "ut": 1630987699,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "Three",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Transport Ministry",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Dilum Amunugama",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka on slippery slope of Enabling Law with expanding gazette rule, emergency: opposition",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka should not resort to excessive control of the people through gazette rule which is an overt sign of authoritarianism and was the principle tool used by Hitler to set up a dictatorship in Germany,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-on-slippery-slope-of-enabling-law-with-expanding-gazette-rule-emergency-opposition-85864/",
    "url_hash": "3c054cabc3b9171221733238637809c7",
    "ut": 1630987711,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Hitler",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Germany",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka on dangerous path of Enabling Law with gazette rule, emergency: opposition",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "ECONOMYNEXT - Sri Lanka should not resort to excessive control of the people through gazette rule which is an overt sign of ... in which the ruling party has a two thirds majority. (Colombo/Sept07/2021)",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-on-dangerous-path-of-enabling-law-with-gazette-rule-emergency-opposition-85864/",
    "url_hash": "29765e7823468eafb48e10895c324c50",
    "ut": 1630987726,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "ECONOMYNEXT - Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two thirds",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka hikes import duty on onions by Rs40 per kilogram",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has hiked import duty on foreign onions by 40 rupees a kilogram to protect domestic farmers, Agriculture Minister Mahindananda Aluthgamage said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-hikes-import-duty-on-onions-by-rs40-per-kilogram-85865/",
    "url_hash": "01e411989f3f3aebb3e7a75257eb833f",
    "ut": 1630988306,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "40",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Agriculture",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Mahindananda Aluthgamage",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          23
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka launches tourism promotion initiatives with Ukraine, Russia",
    "source": "english.newstracklive.com",
    "snippet": "COLOMBO: In a major development in Sri Lanka Tourism, it has launched tourism promotion initiatives with Ukraine and Russia aimed at reviving the sect..|News Track",
    "url": "https://english.newstracklive.com/news/sri-lanka-launches-tourism-promotion-initiatives-with-ukraine-russia-sc57-nu318-ta318-1181053-1.html",
    "url_hash": "23122e619eeb2816c49dfdf14d9cc6b2",
    "ut": 1630990625,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "'The competition is obviously a good thing': Reeza Hendricks pushing hard for T20 World Cup squad",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Reeza Hendricks knows all about being the best man, but never quite the groom. Now with the Proteas squad for the T20 World Cup set to be announced, he once again finds himself in the situation of being left at the altar.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-za/sport/other/the-competition-is-obviously-a-good-thing-reeza-hendricks-pushing-hard-for-t20-world-cup-squad/ar-AAOawL7",
    "url_hash": "2f2323df9bbb579f62a3ed9c13aec2f7",
    "ut": 1630991516,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Proteas",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "EVENT",
        "text": "World Cup",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Covid death toll in Sri Lanka crosses the 10,000 mark",
    "source": "menafn.com",
    "snippet": "The coronavirus death toll in Sri Lanka crossed the 10,000 mark today.   The Ministry of Health said that another 189 dea",
    "url": "https://menafn.com/1102749479/Covid-death-toll-in-Sri-Lanka-crosses-the-10000-mark",
    "url_hash": "1c4374cbc0fb00d9c57de4cfb0314777",
    "ut": 1630992532,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "10,000 mark",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Ministry of Health",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "189",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "SL launches tourism promotion initiatives with Russia, Ukraine",
    "source": "www.sify.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has launched tourism promotion initiatives with Russia and Ukraine aimed at reviving the sector which has been severely hit by the Covid-19 pandemic, a Minister said here.",
    "url": "https://www.sify.com/news/sl-launches-tourism-promotion-initiatives-with-russia-ukraine-news-international-vjhf4ldeifdeg.html",
    "url_hash": "534bda2060921dde38e35ebb24e7a598",
    "ut": 1630992629,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka to award 106mn rupees in prize money to Paralympics winners",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "ECONOMYNEXT - Sri Lanka's cabinet of ministers have approved prize money totalling 106 million rupees to be awarded to the athletes who excelled at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympics and to their coaches. According to the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-to-award-106mn-rupees-in-prize-money-to-paralympics-winners-85869/",
    "url_hash": "8274c9ee1a29d52fe992984cb43884c6",
    "ut": 1630994922,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "ECONOMYNEXT - Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "106 million",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Tokyo 2020 Paralympics",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          43
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-07",
    "title": "Quadruplets of Covid-19 infected mother die at birth",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Four stillborn babies, of a pregnant mother infected with Covid-19, have died during the delivery at the Ampara General Hospital. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Quadruplets-of-Covid-19-infected-mother-die-at-birth/108-219869",
    "url_hash": "1f8df6bd2c4245512b3e16a935396617",
    "ut": 1630995493,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "Four",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Ampara General Hospital",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]