[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-08",
    "title": "Sri Lanka Cricket donates 200 cricket mattings to develop schools cricket",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Cricket donated 200 cricket mattings to the Sri Lanka Schools Cricket Association to be distributed among schools in the country. The donated mattings are now being distributed to schools playing U15,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-cricket-donates-200-cricket-mattings-to-develop-schools-cricket/",
    "url_hash": "8a5778df1a5275f7bc7f7d26429b6759",
    "ut": 1646698593,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Cricket",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "200",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sri Lanka Schools Cricket Association",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "U15",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-08",
    "title": "Sri Lanka should market price energy, re-structure debt, got to IMF: biz chambers",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "ECONOMYNEXT - Sri Lanka top business chambers called for market pricing energy, pre-emptive re-structuring of debt and a program with the International Monetary Fund that would provide confidence to the market and investors. Sri Lanka is seeing severe ...",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-should-market-price-energy-re-structure-debt-got-to-imf-biz-chambers-91394/",
    "url_hash": "7c4ec716fe9e50ce9662155478361ea2",
    "ut": 1646699704,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-08",
    "title": "Sahan Weerasooriya",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "in an effort to continuously support Small and Medium Enterprises in Sri Lanka while... Keynote Address delivered by Panduka Karunanayake Senior Lecturer in the Department of Clinical Medicine, Faculty of Medicine, University of Colombo, at 16th Annual ...",
    "url": "https://island.lk/author/sahanl/page/735/",
    "url_hash": "9e2130738e5a1a45d3ebcae1644f8f29",
    "ut": 1646699713,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Keynote Address",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Panduka Karunanayake Senior Lecturer",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Department of Clinical Medicine, Faculty of Medicine, University of Colombo",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          37
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Annual",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-08",
    "title": "Sri Lanka sharply depreciates currency as crisis bites",
    "source": "www.deccanherald.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka announced a near-15 per cent depreciation of its currency Monday, four days after the IMF called for devaluation and higher taxes to revive the almost-bankrupt economy. The Central Bank of Sri Lanka said it will allow \"greater flexibility\" so that the market will determine the exchange rate,",
    "url": "https://www.deccanherald.com/international/world-news-politics/sri-lanka-sharply-depreciates-currency-as-crisis-bites-1089086.html",
    "url_hash": "10714bd017ee0d3f804569158baaec6e",
    "ut": 1646701667,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "near-15 per cent",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Monday",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "four days",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "IMF",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Central Bank of Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]