[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Punchihewa's new book on King Vijayabahu, the redeemer of Lanka",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "After becoming the ruler of the island, he wanted to bring about economic ... it may mot be wrong to say that King Vijayabahu wass the greatest ruler of Sri Lanka. In enumerating his virtues, a recent researcher scholar said, \"If there is a Sri Lankan ...",
    "url": "https://island.lk/punchihewas-new-book-on-king-vijayabahu-the-redeemer-of-lanka/",
    "url_hash": "76bf7d0af5cbafe88d62b99046e276ba",
    "ut": 1648339271,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "King Vijayabahu",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          51
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "More on wrecks and treasure of the sea off Galle",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sixty years or so later I was in Galle, organizing an international group of maritime archaeologists who were training a clutch of our young archaeology undergraduates and, at the same time, compiling a data base of shipwrecks in Galle Bay.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/more-on-wrecks-and-treasure-of-the-sea-off-galle/",
    "url_hash": "3468e88812cec183c2abd5f51158d10f",
    "ut": 1648339946,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sixty years or so later",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Galle",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Galle Bay",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          43
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Lanka should set up a currency board to stop rupee depreciation: US economist",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka should set up a currency board to stop further currency falls, US economist Steve Hanke has said as the island's currency collapsed from 203 to 290 to the US dollar in an attempt to float the currency which has not yet succeeded.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/lanka-should-set-up-a-currency-board-to-stop-rupee-depreciation-us-economist/",
    "url_hash": "2203d920e2a94f288719286fff09f41d",
    "ut": 1648339950,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Steve Hanke",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "203",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "290",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]