[
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka BOP deficit soars to US$2.7bn to July 2021 as bond auctions fail",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has run a balance of payments deficit of 2.755 billion US dollars up to July 2021, official data show, a record high, as historically high levels of liquidity was injected to expand unsustainable credit,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-bop-deficit-soars-to-us2-7bn-to-july-2021-as-bond-auctions-fail-86094/",
    "url_hash": "7d18a37ebfb51fb2853364ab45316e76",
    "ut": 1631578553,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "2.755 billion US dollars",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "July 2021",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Is it business as usual in 2005?",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Can you get back to business as usual because your life and limbs, your loved ones and your property are all safe? No. The tsunami has wiped away more than life and property in coastal and low-lying areas.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/050109/ft/@home.html",
    "url_hash": "689f0b4e186daa0a37eac98040b3fdd7",
    "ut": 1631579965,
    "ent_info_list": []
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka BOP deficit soars to US$2.7bn up to July as bond auctions fail",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has run a balance of payments deficit of 2.755 billion US dollars up to July 2021, official data show, a record high, as historically high levels of liquidity was injected to expand unsustainable credit,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-bop-deficit-soars-to-us2-7bn-up-to-july-as-bond-auctions-fail-86094/",
    "url_hash": "ed8990c0cf87e56b64d19bef8f9322b5",
    "ut": 1631580149,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "2.755 billion US dollars",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "July 2021",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Post-covid clinics for those with health issues after recovery: Medical specialist",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Claiming that some people who recover from Covid-19 could experience post-covid symptoms such as cough, breathing difficulties and chest pain even after two weeks of recovery, a medical specialist said yesterday such people should seek medical advice.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Post-covid-clinics-for-those-with-health-issues-after-recovery-Medical-specialist/108-220308",
    "url_hash": "7c60e2316b269d03cffc8c52bae8ba86",
    "ut": 1631581693,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "two weeks",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Keep training uninterrupted, the biggest challenge for athletes in centenary year",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Athletics announces calendar for 2022 by Reemus Fernando How to keep training uninterrupted amidst the Covid-19 pandemic to succeed at international events is the biggest problem the track and field athletes need to find answers to in the sport's centenary year in 2022 as Sri Lanka Athletics announced a busy 2022 Competition calendar",
    "url": "https://island.lk/keep-training-uninterrupted-the-biggest-challenge-for-athletes-in-centenary-year/",
    "url_hash": "d57cb93e0ef6391b5f86af053cf91ed8",
    "ut": 1631582233,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Athletics",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2022",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Reemus Fernando",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2022",
        "start_end": [
          45,
          46
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Athletics",
        "start_end": [
          47,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Allianz Lanka wins Claims Initiative of the Year",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Allianz Insurance Lanka Ltd received the prestigious 'Claims Initiative of the Year - Sri Lanka' award at the Insurance Asia Awards 2021 held recently. Organized by Insurance Asia, a renowned publication devoted to insurance companies,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/allianz-lanka-wins-claims-initiative-of-the-year/",
    "url_hash": "f1e950dd9d9ce89caea765da29f659ea",
    "ut": 1631583274,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Allianz Insurance Lanka Ltd",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "EVENT",
        "text": "the Year - Sri Lanka'",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Insurance Asia Awards 2021",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Insurance Asia",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Concerns over civil society engagement with government",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "By Jehan Perera The 48th session of the UN Human Rights Council that started this week in Geneva will not be having any new UN resolutions with regard to Sri Lanka. This session will only see the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/concerns-over-civil-society-engagement-with-government/",
    "url_hash": "8ee37ac0f80a07441c1ca7b7a65d59e2",
    "ut": 1631583303,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Jehan Perera",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "48th",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the UN Human Rights Council",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "this week",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Geneva",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka seek batting stability in dead rubber",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Rex Clementine After a hard fought win in the ODI series, old problems have resurfaced for Sri Lanka in T20 cricket as the team is unable to bat out the 20 overs. Sri Lanka handed the T20 series to the Proteas on Sunday after suffering a heavy nine wicket defeat with 35 balls to",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-seek-batting-stability-in-dead-rubber/",
    "url_hash": "783ab979742b3c906769798d75726e6a",
    "ut": 1631584054,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "ODI",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "20",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Proteas on",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          45
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "nine",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          50
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "35",
        "start_end": [
          53,
          54
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Explained: Sri Lanka's economic crisis",
    "source": "www.theweek.in",
    "snippet": "As rating agencies slashed their estimates for Sri Lanka, food lines formed across the country, and a balance of payments crisis threatened to implode the economy, Sri Lanka's government officials denied the existence of a food crisis in the country.",
    "url": "https://www.theweek.in/news/world/2021/09/13/explained-sri-lankas-economic-crisis.html",
    "url_hash": "f84fc624f8cee830d384fea197274da9",
    "ut": 1631587642,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]