[
  {
    "date": "2021-08-18",
    "title": "Keep all Parties informed of COVID control measures - UNP Leader",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "United National Party Leader, MP Ranil Wickremesinghe has requested President Gotabaya Rajapaksa yesterday (17) to keep all political parties informed of the actions being taken by the Government regarding the COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/keep-all-parties-informed-of-covid-control-measures-unp-leader/ar-AANqOr8",
    "url_hash": "2d78ba940d6145c547d13a7c07ad91b9",
    "ut": 1629246482,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "United National Party",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Ranil Wickremesinghe",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gotabaya Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "17",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-18",
    "title": "Chinese Air Force Iron wings of courage",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The realm of the clouds is the domain of pilots. The Chinese Air Force has a rich heritage embellished with determination and innovation. This branch is the aerial wing of the People's Liberation Army.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/chinese-air-force-iron-wings-of-courage/ar-AANqHI7",
    "url_hash": "b1e9cb0d88eda033e202db654a6e5380",
    "ut": 1629246482,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Chinese Air Force",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the People's Liberation Army",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-18",
    "title": "Sri Lanka CSE says second broker system had glitches after DVP went live",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's Colombo Stock Exchange said a second broker system experienced a glitch when delivery versus payments system was in operation on Tuesday, delaying trading, though there had been no problems in earlier trial runs.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-cse-says-second-broker-system-had-glitches-after-dvp-went-live-85089/",
    "url_hash": "449cc391f1cf14ba1a9f1c08d0600c9a",
    "ut": 1629246487,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Colombo Stock Exchange",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "second",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Tuesday",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-18",
    "title": "Namal's new Ministry to monitor major development projects",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The newly established Development Coordination and Monitoring Ministry has been assigned to monitor a vast number of on-going development activities of the Government from uplifting the livelihoods of Samurdhi beneficiaries to the construction of Expressways.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/namal-s-new-ministry-to-monitor-major-development-projects/ar-AANr1ZQ",
    "url_hash": "563e76b7e77f99a2bcde9d7bf9e83156",
    "ut": 1629246491,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Development Coordination and Monitoring Ministry",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Expressways",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]