[
  {
    "date": "2021-08-06",
    "title": "Thinking about the English visitors",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "But now with the Ashes in it's pockets and a team that is determined, English cricket is in a different position. They are so serious in this endeavor that we learned that some of the cricketers were already in Sri Lanka practicing at the nets even before the rest of the team arrived in the island officially.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/120318/Sports/sunday_Musings.html",
    "url_hash": "d9d15ee085c60670f9fbf2fb0750c21d",
    "ut": 1628209750,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "English",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          44
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-06",
    "title": "Standard Chartered showcases Sri Lanka's potential via China - Sri Lanka Virtual Investor Forum",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Standard Chartered Sri Lanka together with Standard Chartered China recently organised the 'Showcase Sri Lanka: 2021 China - Sri Lanka Virtual Investor Forum' to highlight the partnership potential between the two countries and the emerging strategic opportunities in a shifting global landscape.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/standard-chartered-showcases-sri-lankas-potential-via-china-sri-lanka-virtual-investor-forum/",
    "url_hash": "c82493df652af6d7db8ec687278b120b",
    "ut": 1628210050,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Standard Chartered Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Standard Chartered China",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Showcase Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2021",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "China",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-06",
    "title": "Student Activists and several others arrested for their involvement in protests",
    "source": "www.newsfirst.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Police have arrested student activists for their involvement in the protest that took place close to the parliament on 03rd - Get the latest breaking news and top stories from Sri Lanka, the latest political news,",
    "url": "https://www.newsfirst.lk/2021/08/06/student-activists-and-several-others-arrested-for-their-involvement-in-protests/",
    "url_hash": "a62c64d104bd34d2d745452deb720dfe",
    "ut": 1628211790,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Police",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "03rd",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-08-06",
    "title": "Framework for a new Sri Lanka: A Union of Regions",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "We cannot solve our problems with the same thinking we used when we created them. - Albert Einstein By Raj Gonsalkorale Sri Lanka is in dire economic strife, its politicians are a discredited lot, and are produced by a system that perpetuates corruption,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/framework-for-a-new-sri-lanka-a-union-of-regions/",
    "url_hash": "a5cee7d639ab3c7b6d1eff20d5a10f93",
    "ut": 1628212270,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Albert Einstein",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]