[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Inequality and fallacies in the law - EDITORIAL",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "'Equality before law means, that among equals the law should be equal and should be equally administered, that like should be treated alike. Sadly this description is not always followed in international politics or even in domestic and day-to-day affairs.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/opinion/Inequality-and-fallacies-in-the-law-EDITORIAL/231-232445",
    "url_hash": "40fffca7003bf02787b5adec1465186b",
    "ut": 1646611723,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "day",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          47
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Repealing PTA",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "I often reflect on the tumultuous years of the late 1970s and the paths not taken that may have determined a different future for our country. Emergency rule and then the enactment of the Prevention of Terrorism Act (PTA) in 1979 are unforgettable times of ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/opinion/Repealing-PTA/172-232444",
    "url_hash": "989acc33749856e406a282c84812ddd6",
    "ut": 1646611745,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the tumultuous years of the late 1970s",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Prevention of Terrorism Act",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          39
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "1979",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          44
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka tea prices hit record in Feb 2022, but Russia - Ukraine conflict looms",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka tea prices which hit a record national average of 725 rupees in February, but has is seeing pressure after Russia invaded Ukraine, despite lower volumes offered, auction results show.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-tea-prices-hit-record-in-feb-2022-but-russia-ukraine-conflict-looms-91279/",
    "url_hash": "2f0606fb1f36b19686233d406b839744",
    "ut": 1646611750,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "725",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "February",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Inequality and fallacies in the law - EDITORIAL",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "'Equality before law means, that among equals the law should be equal and should be equally administered, that like should be treated alike. Sadly this description is not always followed in international politics or even in domestic and day-to-day affairs.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/opinion/Inequality-and-fallacies-in-the-law-EDITORIAL/172-232445",
    "url_hash": "518bf2d4d442fc418adc183f53f11b1b",
    "ut": 1646611758,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "day",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          47
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka needs 'Price Formula' to avert future Energy Crisis",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "As Sri Lanka pitches into darkness and its people form lines at fuel stations due to the ongoing energy crisis, its largest import bill, petrol and diesel, had cost an alarming USD 3.7Bn between January to December 2021 which is 18% of the island's total import expenditure.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/sri-lanka-needs-price-formula-to-avert-future-energy-crisis/ar-AAUHRPx",
    "url_hash": "4301108da896bec40098e3d6c8635644",
    "ut": 1646611767,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "between January to December 2021",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          41
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERCENT",
        "text": "18%",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          45
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka: A geopolitical magnet in the Indian Ocean Region",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Located 50 kilometres from Hindustan or the Republic of India, the island country of Sri Lanka has never suffered from a lack of attention from the world's leading players. This is due to the island's critical strategic position in the Indian Ocean Region (IOR).",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/sri-lanka-a-geopolitical-magnet-in-the-indian-ocean-region/ar-AAUHRQ6",
    "url_hash": "039536c4ed2293dcb6d73d77eb2a48cc",
    "ut": 1646612730,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "QUANTITY",
        "text": "50 kilometres",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Hindustan",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "the Republic of India",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Indian Ocean Region",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          47
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "IOR",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          49
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lankan shares drop over 2% ahead of central bank rate decision",
    "source": "cn.reuters.com",
    "snippet": "The International Monetary Fund said on Wednesday that Sri Lanka needs to tighten its monetary policy to contain rising inflation and reverse one of the worst financial crises the island-nation has faced in years. * The crisis has also led to an acute fuel ...",
    "url": "https://cn.reuters.com/article/sri-lanka-markets-close-idCNL3N2V60P4",
    "url_hash": "9ac196841be4c5aa9d4c1cd774e4d773",
    "ut": 1646612730,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "years",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Ukraine crisis batters Sri Lanka's tea and tourism recovery strategy",
    "source": "www.ft.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka faces an escalating debt crisis after Russia's invasion of Ukraine wrecked two of its largest tourist markets, with analysts warning that the economic fallout of the c",
    "url": "https://www.ft.com/content/3a6d3822-7c7a-4c62-9a0e-dcff37e2a175",
    "url_hash": "eef70ef08fa98dccd854117eeee9f4e9",
    "ut": 1646612742,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka tea pressured after hitting record in Feb 2022 as Russia invades Ukraine",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka tea prices which hit a record national average of 725 rupees in February, but has is seeing pressure after Russia invaded Ukraine, despite lower volumes offered, auction results show.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-tea-pressured-after-hitting-record-in-feb-2022-as-russia-invades-ukraine-91279/",
    "url_hash": "f34934d0afa652b8a49749f9222b3d67",
    "ut": 1646612748,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "725",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "February",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Pakistan: A Breathtaking Tourist Destination",
    "source": "en.ce.cn",
    "snippet": "The U.S. magazine Condé Nast Traveler ranked Pakistan as No.1 travel destination for tourism in 2020. Taxila (editor's note: a city in Rawalpindi District of Punjab, Pakistan), an ancient city, is a trove of treasures with Buddhist Stupas and archeological remains and the tales tell us that Thomas the Apostle came to present day Taxila in the first century AD.",
    "url": "https://en.ce.cn/main/latest/202203/07/t20220307_37380312.shtml",
    "url_hash": "3f053b1c2ba5c33f9773d540c7f56401",
    "ut": 1646615346,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "U.S.",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Condé Nast Traveler",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2020",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Rawalpindi District of Punjab",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Buddhist",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          45
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Thomas the Apostle",
        "start_end": [
          55,
          58
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the first century AD",
        "start_end": [
          64,
          68
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka suffer third heaviest defeat in Tests",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Rex Clementine in Mohali Sri Lanka were cut to size by a formidable India side as the first Test between the countries ended inside three days handing the hosts a massive innings and 222 run win. This is Sri Lanka's third heaviest defeat as 16 wickets fell on a maniac day as India went 1-0",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-suffer-third-heaviest-defeat-in-tests/",
    "url_hash": "a54f47d5c454b1599c513163f553500d",
    "ut": 1646616330,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Rex Clementine",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Mohali Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "first",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "three days",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "222",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "third",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          43
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "16",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          47
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "a maniac day",
        "start_end": [
          50,
          53
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          54,
          55
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "1",
        "start_end": [
          56,
          57
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Geneva sessions: India ratchets up pressure on Lanka to hold PC polls",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "India has again called for early Provincial Council elections in Sri Lanka, at the Geneva-based United Nations.  India's Permanent Representative in Geneva, Ambassador Indra Mani Pande, during the interactive session on Match 4 on the OHCHR's written report on promoting reconciliation,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/geneva-sessions-india-ratchets-up-pressure-on-lanka-to-hold-pc-polls/",
    "url_hash": "a1eb8510b36042db02d728c5b22b961b",
    "ut": 1646616330,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Provincial Council",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Geneva",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "United Nations",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Permanent Representative",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Geneva",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Indra Mani Pande",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LAW",
        "text": "Match 4",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          41
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "OHCHR",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          44
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Pakistan: A Breathtaking Tourist Destination",
    "source": "en.ce.cn",
    "snippet": "The U.S. magazine Condé Nast Traveler ranked Pakistan as No.1 travel destination for tourism in 2020. Taxila (editor's note: a city in Rawalpindi District of Punjab, Pakistan), an ancient city, is a trove of treasures with Buddhist Stupas and archeological remains and the tales tell us that Thomas the Apostle came to present day Taxila in the first century AD.",
    "url": "http://en.ce.cn/main/latest/202203/07/t20220307_37380312.shtml",
    "url_hash": "c8d65f845cbc83ce0c03c068e7758339",
    "ut": 1646617122,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "U.S.",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Condé Nast Traveler",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2020",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Rawalpindi District of Punjab",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Buddhist",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          45
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Thomas the Apostle",
        "start_end": [
          55,
          58
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the first century AD",
        "start_end": [
          64,
          68
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "President to open state-of-the-art Lanwa Sanstha Cement factory in H'tota today",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "State-of-the-art cement manufacturing facility of Lanwa Sanstha Cement Corporation (Pvt) Ltd is slated to be declared open today by the President Gotabaya Rajapaksa. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/President-to-open-state-of-the-art-Lanwa-Sanstha-Cement-factory-in-Htota-today/108-232466",
    "url_hash": "11d22380fd89f3faea72006ff752b711",
    "ut": 1646618923,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Lanwa Sanstha Cement Corporation",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gotabaya Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Pan Asia Bank relocates Pillimathalawa branch",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Pan Asia Bank relocated its Pilimathalawa branch, on March 2, 2022, to No.217, Kandy Road, Manadeniya, Pilimathalawa. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/financial-news/Pan-Asia-Bank-relocates-Pillimathalawa-branch/265-232455",
    "url_hash": "04b45dbc27c8ce771eceef54f1295984",
    "ut": 1646618923,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Pan Asia Bank",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Pilimathalawa",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "March 2, 2022",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kandy Road",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Manadeniya",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Central Bank seeks price revision to fuel, electricity at least to cover cost",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Central Bank wants the government to revise the price of fuel and electricity at least to cover the full cost of bringing them to the end consumer in order to end the external and fiscal sector woes created by the loss making State-run utilities in the country.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business-news/Central-Bank-seeks-price-revision-to-fuel-electricity-at-least-to-cover-cost/273-232463",
    "url_hash": "d808d60367da0d8238dd7a9524214416",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Central Bank",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "State",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          44
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "H'tota Port declares 2022 as 'Year of Construction'",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Hambantota International Port (HIP) has declared 2022 as a 'Year of Construction', with several ongoing projects reaching different stages of building their respective plants in the Port's Industrial park.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/other/Htota-Port-declares-2022-as-Year-of-Construction/117-232462",
    "url_hash": "c40dc117728f26ccfa0e182a767312c3",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Hambantota International Port",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2022",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "IFC reaffirms commitment to Sri Lanka amid plans to increase investments",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "IFC, the private sector investment arm of the World Bank said it is looking to invest over US$ 800 million in Sri Lanka over the next five years in the sustainable infrastructure sector. The development lender also revealed its plans to invest a further US$ 150 million during the current financial year ending June 2022 in addition to the US$ 450 million it had invested in the first 18 months of th .",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business-news/IFC-reaffirms-commitment-to-Sri-Lanka-amid-plans-to-increase-investments/273-232465",
    "url_hash": "1d7b8bcf48756651ddb9d67d2848dc8c",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the World Bank",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "US$ 800 million",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the next five years",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "US$ 150 million",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          49
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the current financial year ending June 2022",
        "start_end": [
          50,
          57
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "US$ 450 million",
        "start_end": [
          61,
          64
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the first 18 months",
        "start_end": [
          68,
          72
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Non-fungible tokens: Fool's gold or a glimpse of the future?",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Early January of 2022 is marked by anticipation of things to come. Global economies are gearing up to put the pandemic behind them and face the uncertainties of a world whose normalcy has been altered beyond recognition.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/businessopinion/Non-fungible-tokens-Fools-gold-or-a-glimpse-of-the-future/306-232458",
    "url_hash": "a5a7537bad04c97c2790f55e0b94aef7",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Early January of 2022",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "People's Bank's consolidated financial support extended during 2020 & 2021 crosses Rs.1tn",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Announcing the financial performance for the year ended December 31, 2021, People's Bank said it reported a consolidated operating income of Rs.110.7 billion and total operating expenses amounted to Rs.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business-news/Peoples-Banks-consolidated-financial-support-extended-during-2020-2021-crosses-Rs-1tn/273-232468",
    "url_hash": "01d3e5eb18e7c39a3f4188ec6dd5bd07",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the year ended December 31, 2021",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "People's Bank",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "Rs.110.7 billion",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Kusal Jayawardana appointed as Alliance Finance Deputy Managing Director",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Kusal Jayawardana has been appointed as Deputy Managing Director of Alliance Finance Company PLC (AFC), with effect from March 1, 2022 and prior to his new appointment, he served on the board of AFC as Executive Director Finance and Operations,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/financial-news/Kusal-Jayawardana-appointed-as-Alliance-Finance-Deputy-Managing-Director/265-232453",
    "url_hash": "7fd38efd8e077b42a182fb1cf44f88fe",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kusal Jayawardana",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Alliance Finance Company PLC",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "March 1, 2022",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "AFC",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Operations",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          45
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "CPM ranks ComBank among top 10 best-managed firms",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Institute of Chartered Professional Managers of Sri Lanka (CPM) has ranked Commercial Bank of Ceylon among the 10 best-managed companies in Sri Lanka in the two years affected by the global pandemic.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/financial-news/CPM-ranks-ComBank-among-top-10-best-managed-firms/265-232456",
    "url_hash": "1352f72af4e6692c31972d3b13b885f5",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Institute of Chartered Professional Managers of Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "CPM",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Commercial Bank of Ceylon",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "10",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the two years",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "MBSL marks a strong turnaround in 2021",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Merchant Bank of Sri Lanka and Finance PLC (MBSL) announced yesterday that it has made a strong turnaround in 2O21. It has reported Rs.812 million as profit before tax (PBT) for 2021, compared to a loss of Rs.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/financial-news/MBSL-marks-a-strong-turnaround-in-2021/265-232454",
    "url_hash": "01563f87a1b894213adb9694eabb886d",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Merchant Bank of Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "Rs.812 million",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2021",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Colombo Dockyard builds and delivers Underwater Restaurant Structure for Maldivian resort",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Colombo Dockyard PLC (CDPLC) has contracted with Promonant Pvt Ltd (client) of Maldives for the design, supply of materials, fabrication, towingand providing installation guidance of an Underwater Restaurant Structure (UWRS) planned to be placed at Aanugandu Falhu Island in the Republic of Maldives.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/other/Colombo-Dockyard-builds-and-delivers-Underwater-Restaurant-Structure-for-Maldivian-resort/117-232461",
    "url_hash": "58e465a790117da433dbe821bd86757d",
    "ut": 1646618945,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "CDPLC",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Promonant Pvt Ltd",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Maldives",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "an Underwater Restaurant Structure",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          36
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UWRS",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          38
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Aanugandu Falhu Island",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          47
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "the Republic of Maldives",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          52
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Govt. looking at holistic approach to digitally transform SL: Namal",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Dedicated efforts are underway to transform Sri Lanka into a technology-based society, as the government is actively looking at a holistic approach to create an ecosystem where citizen services will be supported by digital transformation,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business-news/Govt-looking-at-holistic-approach-to-digitally-transform-SL-Namal/273-232467",
    "url_hash": "487222c7ec99a247c51dcb751491a818",
    "ut": 1646618955,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "CB continues to resist IMF-led debt restructuring to end foreign exchange crisis",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Central Bank is still disinclined to recommend to the government to seek International Monetary Fund (IMF) support for a rescue package and foreign currency debt restructuring even amid the country in a deeper foreign exchange crisis,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business__main/CB-continues-to-resist-IMF-led-debt-restructuring-to-end-foreign-exchange-crisis/245-232470",
    "url_hash": "d13687e9fe4f4f24c816c004b4decfbe",
    "ut": 1646618958,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Central Bank",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Govt. looking at holistic approach to digitally transform SL: Namal",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Dedicated efforts are underway to transform Sri Lanka into a technology-based society, as the government is actively looking at a holistic approach to create an ecosystem where citizen services will be supported by digital transformation,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Govt-looking-at-holistic-approach-to-digitally-transform-SL-Namal/108-232467",
    "url_hash": "3609697155cab63e8fc6db9e597dd97f",
    "ut": 1646618967,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Low-pressure area's impact on Sri Lanka's weather reducing",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "The low-pressure area in the Southwest Bay of Bengal is weakening and its impact on the island's weather is reducing, says the Department of Meteorology",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news.php?nid=81028",
    "url_hash": "412ba381e67cab63fd7143380d73bafb",
    "ut": 1646622532,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Southwest Bay",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Bengal",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Department of Meteorology",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          29
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Public protests continue in SL against govt. failures",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Public protests continued on Sunday evening as several people gathered with candles in Kohuwala and Rajagiriya to protest against the severe day to day hardships caused by the economic failure of the government.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/main_image/Public-protests-continue-in-SL-against-govt-failures/346-232487",
    "url_hash": "bea4d0c106e50156a5d984d324d7a78e",
    "ut": 1646622539,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "evening",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Kohuwala",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Rajagiriya",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Bonus interest scheme for senior citizen deposits extended by one year",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "However, deposits maintained under the scheme will not be auto-renewed Deposit holders will have to make a declaration to the bank to make available the special interest rate at maturity The Central Bank has extended the 15 percent special interest scheme ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/business-news/Bonus-interest-scheme-for-senior-citizen-deposits-extended-by-one-year/273-232469",
    "url_hash": "218f30738a2ffec15bc7ac877435060c",
    "ut": 1646622545,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Central Bank",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          36
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERCENT",
        "text": "15 percent",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Union Assurance Circle of Excellence relaunches with bigger and better rewards",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Union Assurance Circle of Excellence, the most exclusive bancassurance rewards scheme in the Sri Lankan insurance industry, has been relaunched with a bigger and better rewards scheme to recognise the company's high-performing insurance relationship ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/financial-news/Union-Assurance-Circle-of-Excellence-relaunches-with-bigger-and-better-rewards/265-232457",
    "url_hash": "c15ff05f40b3225e7c95ae29e4156e12",
    "ut": 1646622545,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Union Assurance Circle of Excellence",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Low-pressure area's impact on Sri Lanka's weather reducing",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "The low-pressure area in the Southwest Bay of Bengal is weakening and its impact on the island's weather is reducing, says the Department of Meteorology",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news/81028/low-pressure-areas-impact-on-sri-lankas-weather-reducing",
    "url_hash": "0433ef82536ce78610b1e40e204c40ae",
    "ut": 1646622555,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Southwest Bay",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Bengal",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Department of Meteorology",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          29
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Ceremonial tusker 'Nadungamuwa Raja' dies",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "Nadungamuwa Raja' the tusker which had carried the sacred relic casket of the Kandy Esala Perahera the most number of times, has died this morning at the age of 69 years",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news.php?nid=81029",
    "url_hash": "4f9e337837d503947b1db0406c78b4ff",
    "ut": 1646622555,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nadungamuwa Raja'",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "this morning",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the age of 69 years",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Sri Lanka central bank net reserves negative by US$3.2bn in Jan 2022",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Foreign exchange liabilities of Sri Lanka's central bank has exceeded its reserve assets by 662 billion rupees (US$3.29bn) in January 2022, up from 386 billion rupees (US$1.9bn) a month earlier as it got deeper into debt to repay debt and provide reserves for imports,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-central-bank-net-reserves-negative-by-us3-2bn-in-jan-2022-91290/",
    "url_hash": "c4761d13ee5913d9d3ff99f82857d6a2",
    "ut": 1646622993,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "662 billion rupees",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "3.29bn",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "January 2022",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "386 billion",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "1.9bn",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "a month earlier",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Global pandemic deaths near 6m, WHO says",
    "source": "global.chinadaily.com.cn",
    "snippet": "AJIT SOLANKI/AP GENEVA－The number of COVID-19 deaths worldwide is close to 6 million, according to the latest data from the World Health Organization. Globally, there have been 440,807,756 confirmed COVID-19 cases with 5,",
    "url": "https://global.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202203/07/WS622564f5a310cdd39bc8accf.html",
    "url_hash": "653abcffbfe92537e9bb2a6144885985",
    "ut": 1646625084,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "AJIT SOLANKI/AP",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "close to 6 million",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the World Health Organization",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "440,807,756",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "5",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "SLPP edges closer to form new govt; MR urgently calls for political calm",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "In addition to the economic, fuel, power and food crisis which has severely hampered the daily lives of all citizens in the country, Sri Lanka has now been plunged into severe political turmoil after two cabinet ministers were sacked last week and 11 dissident members are now threatening to leave the government.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/top_story/SLPP-edges-closer-to-form-new-govt-MR-urgently-calls-for-political-calm/155-232490",
    "url_hash": "07b6bfa56bf60f570338abb0b8356a32",
    "ut": 1646626123,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          38
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "last week",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "11",
        "start_end": [
          45,
          46
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Severe gas shortage due to forex issue",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The country is currently facing a severe gas shortage as three gas tankers are being anchored off the Sri Lankan waters due to the non-issuance of letters of credit by Sri Lankan commercial banks in the face of the dollar crisis. Informed sources said that ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Severe-gas-shortage-due-to-forex-issue/342-232492",
    "url_hash": "1415666e1c5a35bd62e203f0e2200ed0",
    "ut": 1646626158,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "three",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Private buses get diesel at SLTB depots",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Due to shortage of diesel in fuel stations, private buses are allowed to get the required diesel from the depots owned by the Sri Lanka Transport Board (SLTB). Pix by Nisal Baduge ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/caption_story/Private-buses-get-diesel-at-SLTB-depots/110-232493",
    "url_hash": "e7ef57379b3811909c1fc673461158fc",
    "ut": 1646626158,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sri Lanka Transport Board",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nisal Baduge",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Nadungamuwa Raja dies",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Nadungamuwa Vijaya Raja, popularly known as Nadungamuwa Raja passed away this morning, the caretaker of the elephant Harsha Dharmawijeya said. He said the elephant died at 5.30 am today following a brief illness. \"The majestic animal did not have previous ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Nadungamuwa-Raja-dies/342-232488",
    "url_hash": "1d5147ccb384e49d2e1547e328f46e1c",
    "ut": 1646626158,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nadungamuwa Vijaya Raja",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Nadungamuwa Raja",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "this morning",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Harsha Dharmawijeya",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "5.30 am",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "A master on field, enigmatic off; Shane Warne dies aged 52",
    "source": "www.kentucky.com",
    "snippet": "Shane Warne's artful and record-breaking spin bowling on the cricket field was matched by his impish allure and often controversial career off the pitch.",
    "url": "https://www.kentucky.com/entertainment/celebrities/article259087468.html",
    "url_hash": "4a8acccee2b287b7d435a4506c3a9115",
    "ut": 1646626158,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Shane Warne's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Con Dao, Phong Nha-Ke Bang among Asia's lesser-known 'stunning' destinations",
    "source": "e.vnexpress.net",
    "snippet": "Canadian travel site The Travel has listed Con Dao Islands and Phong Nha-Ke Bang National Park among '10 stunning destinations in Asia that few people know.'",
    "url": "https://e.vnexpress.net/news/places/con-dao-phong-nha-ke-bang-among-asias-lesser-known-stunning-destinations-4435704.html",
    "url_hash": "c7069f61b9913c1acf8839b761179e24",
    "ut": 1646626167,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Canadian",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Travel",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Con Dao",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Islands",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Phong Nha-Ke Bang",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "10",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Asia",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Severe gas shortage due to forex issue",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The country is currently facing a severe gas shortage as three gas tankers are being anchored off the Sri Lankan waters due to the non-issuance of letters of credit by Sri Lankan commercial banks in the face of the dollar crisis.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/A-severe-gas-shortage-due-to-forex-issue/108-232492",
    "url_hash": "d6a80d664710db2792203f3576881879",
    "ut": 1646626483,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "three",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "2021: Global house price boom slowing, but the U.S., Pacific and some parts of Europe continue to grow strongly",
    "source": "www.globalpropertyguide.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's housing market continues to struggle ... In fact the Puerto Rican housing market been falling continuously for most of the decade. The island has experienced a prolonged economic crisis, massive debt, high unemployment and continuing ...",
    "url": "https://www.globalpropertyguide.com/investment-analysis/2021-Global-house-price-boom-slowing-but-the-US-Pacific-and-some-parts-of-Europe-continue-to-grow-strongly",
    "url_hash": "e140352f5eda1521e4ddce5aa779dab0",
    "ut": 1646628292,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Puerto Rican",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the decade",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Brent crude nears $140 per barrel, headed towards all-time high",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Brent oil prices soared to a near 14-year high of $140 on Sunday as traders fretted over the fallout from Russia's invasion of Ukraine. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Brent-crude-nears-140-per-barrel-headed-towards-all-time-high/108-232502",
    "url_hash": "416a3e7b9c7c4cd393e6c4f5614f9c2f",
    "ut": 1646629739,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "14-year",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "140",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "SriLankan Airlines Partners with Manta Air to Connect Passengers from Gan Island to Koodhdhoo City in Maldives",
    "source": "bizenglish.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "SriLankan Airlines enters into a strategic partnership with Manta Air to offer passengers a seamless travel experience with convenient connections from Gan International Airport to Koodhdhoo City in Gaafu Alifu Atoll of Southern Maldives.",
    "url": "http://bizenglish.adaderana.lk/srilankan-airlines-partners-with-manta-air-to-connect-passengers-from-gan-island-to-koodhdhoo-city-in-maldives/",
    "url_hash": "cbde51d8b65c86bf3c9b8b955b8e74b1",
    "ut": 1646633349,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SriLankan Airlines",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Manta Air",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Gan International Airport",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Koodhdhoo City",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gaafu Alifu Atoll",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Russia's war on Ukraine adds more turmoil to global shipping",
    "source": "www.ft.com",
    "snippet": "The fallout from the war has increased the risk of Sri Lanka defaulting. Now, one local analyst says it's extinguished all hope of resolving the country's economic crisis. You can read more about all these stories at FT.com. If you aren't yet a ...",
    "url": "https://www.ft.com/content/396a7101-e08d-45bc-a20d-239c260b2e08",
    "url_hash": "70f00a8b9cb287343de8efa47dc5f0ae",
    "ut": 1646633362,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "one",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "FT.com",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          43
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-07",
    "title": "Cracks Appear In Sri Lanka's Coalition Government After Sacking Of Two Cabinet Ministers",
    "source": "www.republicworld.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's Water Supply Minister Vasudeva Nanayakkara on Monday said he will boycott cabinet meetings to protest the sacking of his two colleagues by President Gotabaya Rajapaksa during a snap cabinet reshuffle last week,",
    "url": "https://www.republicworld.com/world-news/rest-of-the-world-news/cracks-appear-in-sri-lankas-coalition-government-after-sacking-of-two-cabinet-ministers.html",
    "url_hash": "fe36c2192661dd09580b1e9b0a1c037f",
    "ut": 1646636049,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Vasudeva Nanayakkara",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Monday",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gotabaya Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "last week",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]