[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "Regulator of Sri Lanka Tourism urged to show 'sanity over vanity' on new draft bill",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sanath Nanayakkare Major hoteliers and leading tour operators in the country yesterday urged the Sri Lanka Tourism Development Authority (SLTDA) to take their views on board before the tabling of the news Bill on Tourism in Parliament.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/regulator-of-sri-lanka-tourism-urged-to-show-sanity-over-vanity-on-new-draft-bill/",
    "url_hash": "09d7af54da385163a2ff18bd24317648",
    "ut": 1646957747,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sanath Nanayakkare",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Sri Lanka Tourism Development Authority",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Parliament",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "Mendis is back and needs to rise to the occasion",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Rex Clementine in Bangalore Sri Lanka's net session at Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bangalore yesterday was taking place behind closed doors. The session was limited for the press and the local cricket authorities.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/mendis-is-back-and-needs-to-rise-to-the-occasion/",
    "url_hash": "e1ec6f5426857553d8704771096723bb",
    "ut": 1646958182,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Rex Clementine",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Chinnaswamy Stadium",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Bangalore",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "No sexual dysfunction from COVID, Health Ministry responds to media reports",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Responding to several media reports that state that some young people who are infected with COVID-19, are susceptible to sexual dysfunction and subfertility, the Health Ministry said there is no any truth behind such claims. Speaking to Daily Mirror, COVID ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/No-sexual-dysfunction-from-COVID-Health-Ministry-responds-to-media-reports/108-232797",
    "url_hash": "b62d6fc253e363df9dfc83b08913dcad",
    "ut": 1646958457,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Health Ministry",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "IFC and Colombo Stock Exchange Ring the Bell for Gender Equality in Sri Lanka",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "For the seventh consecutive year, IFC partnered with the Colombo Stock Exchange (CSE) to 'Ring the Bell for Gender Equality.' Celebrated in line with the International Women's Day, the annual global initiative highlights how greater participation of women in the economy can spur sustainable and inclusive growth,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/ifc-and-colombo-stock-exchange-ring-the-bell-for-gender-equality-in-sri-lanka/",
    "url_hash": "bfb48dad5c57c852d53f89df8b5a4788",
    "ut": 1646958967,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the seventh consecutive year",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Colombo Stock Exchange",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "CSE",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the International Women's Day",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "Sri Lanka actions to stabilize economy in global turmoil: Cabraal",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's actions including a float of the currency and taxes on imported items will help the economy stabilize amid global turmoil, Central Bank Governor Nivard Cabraal said, as the rupee fell in an free float exercise.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-actions-to-stabilize-economy-in-global-turmoil-cabraal-91525/",
    "url_hash": "c4d89970737030c69c343909090cb94b",
    "ut": 1646958984,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Central Bank",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nivard Cabraal",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          29
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "ADB President pledges continuous support to Sri Lanka's development efforts",
    "source": "www.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "Mr. Masatsugu Asakawa says the projects that have been implemented in the island with the assistance of the ADB have made significant strides and he pledged to support Sri Lanka's development efforts continuously.",
    "url": "http://www.adaderana.lk/news.php?nid=81118",
    "url_hash": "5d1a7700dd3cf57046a48493e4bad044",
    "ut": 1646962067,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Masatsugu Asakawa",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-11",
    "title": "Maldivian to fly to Sri Lanka's Ratmalana airport",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Island Aviation Services Limited of Maldives will fly to Sri Lanka's Ratmalana Airport twice a week in the first international scheduled flights in 50 years, the state airport agency said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/maldivian-to-fly-to-sri-lankas-ratmalana-airport-91529/",
    "url_hash": "38283b84ca6d2dabaa3fcc15d5ef7c03",
    "ut": 1646962067,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Island Aviation Services Limited of Maldives",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Ratmalana Airport",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "twice a week",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "first",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "50 years",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]