[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Sri Lanka asks for food aid",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "China has offered 2,000 metric tonnes of rice free of charge, following cash-strapped Sri Lanka's request for urgent food aid. The Chinese Embassy spokesperson said that Ambassador Qi Zhenhong recently informed Premier Mahinda Rajapaksa of their decision to provide 2,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-asks-for-food-aid/",
    "url_hash": "7b4249260f39579f8e9f39cac9c519bb",
    "ut": 1648426270,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "China",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "QUANTITY",
        "text": "2,000 metric tonnes",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Chinese Embassy",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Qi Zhenhong",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Mahinda Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          39
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "2",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          45
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Sri Lanka is facing 'clear solvency problem': IMF report",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "The full report provides further analysis of the South Asian island nation's debt and finances. A summary of the report released earlier in the month said Sri Lanka faced unsustainable debt levels and needed a \"credible and coherent\" strategy to ...",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-is-facing-clear-solvency-problem-imf-report/",
    "url_hash": "a2128e426499b95dcd432624a58221dc",
    "ut": 1648426270,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "South Asian",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "earlier in the month",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          30
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "More on cloud seeding",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Minister of Energy, Pavithra Wanniarachchi, complained to reporters that all of the island's reservoir levels are depleted, therefore reducing their ability to produce hydro-electricity, which in turn results in frequent power cuts.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/more-on-cloud-seeding/",
    "url_hash": "6c4bb720fbd4fa00d0664100928cbfc5",
    "ut": 1648426343,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Pavithra Wanniarachchi",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Multipronged bid to 'democratically' topple the Govt.",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "The mood was one of unease and even sombre when government parliamentarians met at \"Temple Trees\" for their group meeting last Tuesday, one for which President Gotabaya Rajapaksa declared attendance was compulsory. Walking to a 'bar' in a far corner of the venue to help themselves to tots of Black Label Scotch whisky, they chatted to each other about what the coming days and weeks would hold. Some were worried about going back to their electorates where public anger was mounting. Others were concerned about how they would have their party branches ready for a future...",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220327/columns/multipronged-bid-to-democratically-topple-the-govt-478210.html",
    "url_hash": "f2eb6bfd3bbf463213dd2bfccd4eebb9",
    "ut": 1648426596,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
        "text": "Temple Trees",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "last Tuesday",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "one",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gotabaya Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Black Label Scotch",
        "start_end": [
          55,
          58
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the coming days",
        "start_end": [
          67,
          70
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "weeks",
        "start_end": [
          71,
          72
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Sri Lanka Tourism's Influencer Programme continues to create global buzz",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Tourism's travel influencer facilitation program (also known as Visiting Blogger Program) has undertaken creative influencer promotional campaigns by covering diversified tourism experiences from around the island,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/sri-lanka-tourism-s-influencer-programme-continues-to-create-global-buzz/ar-AAVyN5U",
    "url_hash": "a6c10a2818d469705af01e4cf53d1dac",
    "ut": 1648426769,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Visiting Blogger Program",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          15
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Sri Lanka currency board will preserve currency, impose discipline: Wijewardena",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "A currency board for Sri Lanka will stabilize the rupee for the future and impose discipline on both politicians as well as monetary authority officials who want to print money, top economist W A Wijewardena has said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-currency-board-will-preserve-currency-impose-discipline-wijewardena-92125/",
    "url_hash": "6bde49ed7ab4a3c83edecd2a427a7125",
    "ut": 1648427902,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PRODUCT",
        "text": "W A Wijewardena",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Indian External Affairs Minister in Sri Lanka for BIMSTEC & Bilateral talks",
    "source": "www.newsfirst.lk",
    "snippet": "Indian External Affairs Minister Dr. S. Jaishankar arrived in Sri Lana on Sunday (27) night for bilateral talks with Sri Lanka's top - Get the latest breaking news and top stories from Sri Lanka, the latest political news,",
    "url": "https://www.newsfirst.lk/2022/03/28/indian-external-affairs-minister-in-sri-lanka-for-bimstec-bilateral-talks/",
    "url_hash": "2fa75f8a6205f2512c1807bf9a46137f",
    "ut": 1648427991,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Indian External Affairs",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "S. Jaishankar",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lana",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "27) night",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          37
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Launch of Galaxy S22: Samsung Student Ambassadors and Members applaud innovation",
    "source": "colombogazette.com",
    "snippet": "Samsung, Sri Lanka's No. 1 Smartphone Brand, recently unveiled their latest premium flagship series, the Samsung Galaxy S22. The event, which included Samsung's Student Ambassadors and Members, took off on a high note and received phenomenal feedback in response.",
    "url": "https://colombogazette.com/2022/03/28/launch-of-galaxy-s22-samsung-student-ambassadors-and-members-applaud-innovation/",
    "url_hash": "9417e588a915612532e6c55bbbca1f03",
    "ut": 1648429151,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Samsung",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "1",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Samsung Galaxy S22",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Samsung",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Student Ambassadors",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Sunlight partners with Small Enterprises Development Division to uplift SMEs through 'Manudam Viyamana'",
    "source": "colombogazette.com",
    "snippet": "Unilever Sri Lanka, under its flagship brand Sunlight ... Inspired by the resilience and compassion of Sri Lankans around the island who continue to exemplify the power of collective action, the brand will contribute Rs.1/= from each Sunlight Powder ...",
    "url": "https://colombogazette.com/2022/03/28/sunlight-partners-with-small-enterprises-development-division-to-uplift-smes-through-manudam-viyamana/",
    "url_hash": "28a3d4d80b770beb04967ec3a563b008",
    "ut": 1648429311,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Unilever Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lankans",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Sri Lankan SEP/IYSSE holds well attended online meeting against US-NATO war drive and the Russian invasion of Ukraine",
    "source": "www.wsws.org",
    "snippet": "The speakers emphasized that the opposition of the working class to the war is needed to be developed as a conscious political movement for socialism.",
    "url": "https://www.wsws.org/en/articles/2022/03/28/slme-m28.html",
    "url_hash": "0e45b5eeb8cc3221b444bc75ab72abb7",
    "ut": 1648429996,
    "ent_info_list": []
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "MEA Jaishankar To Reach Sri Lanka On Monday For Bilateral Talks And BIMSTEC Summit",
    "source": "www.outlookindia.com",
    "snippet": "This will be Eternal Affairs Minister S Jaishankar's maiden visit to the island nation since India extended an economic relief package to bail Sri Lanka out of the current economic crisis.",
    "url": "https://www.outlookindia.com/national/mea-jaishankar-to-reach-sri-lanka-on-monday-for-bilateral-talks-and-bimstec-summit-news-188813",
    "url_hash": "3025da7290671a0680e26deecc30dae7",
    "ut": 1648432145,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Eternal Affairs",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "S Jaishankar's",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Jaishankar arrives in Lanka to hold bilateral talks, attend BIMSTEC summit",
    "source": "www.business-standard.com",
    "snippet": "External Affairs Minister S Jaishankar arrived here on Sunday to hold bilateral talks with Sri Lanka's top leadership and attend the seven-nation BIMSTEC summit.",
    "url": "https://www.business-standard.com/article/current-affairs/jaishankar-arrives-in-lanka-to-hold-bilateral-talks-attend-bimstec-summit-122032700833_1.html",
    "url_hash": "e7e917a09a6b171b9ee004a2943e28be",
    "ut": 1648432865,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "External Affairs",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "S Jaishankar",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "seven",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "BIMSTEC",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "\"Sri Lanka Travel Deals\" to revolutionize the travel industry",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "\"Sri Lanka Travel Deals\" a destination marketing platform operated by Travel Lead Lanka (Pvt) Ltd, aims to facilitate the tourism industry by offering travellers a host of travel deals when planning their visit to the island. Keeping in mind the ...",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/sri-lanka-travel-deals-to-revolutionize-the-travel-industry/ar-AAVyza9",
    "url_hash": "82756e40333a221932eb0b467e4833ee",
    "ut": 1648433165,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Travel Deals",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          5
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Russian Foreign Minister to visit Delhi this week amid Ukraine war",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov will visit Delhi this week for official meetings, as the war in Ukraine completes one month, sources confirmed. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Russian-Foreign-Minister-to-visit-Delhi-this-week-amid-Ukraine-war/108-233949",
    "url_hash": "80016d972efe7a585be8072c9f46b938",
    "ut": 1648433336,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Russian",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sergei Lavrov",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Delhi",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "this week",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "one month",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "BIMSTEC opens in Colombo on Monday (28)",
    "source": "www.newsfirst.lk",
    "snippet": "The Bay of Bengal Multi-Sectoral Technical and Economic Cooperation or BIMSTEC — the regional organisation exclusive to the Bay, will - Get the latest breaking news and top stories from Sri Lanka, the latest political news,",
    "url": "https://www.newsfirst.lk/2022/03/28/bimstec-opens-in-colombo-on-monday-28/",
    "url_hash": "7131fdb8a98d46f022a63b7023d99010",
    "ut": 1648435709,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "BIMSTEC",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Bay",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "Indian Navy engages in a week-long Advanced Light Helicopter training in Lanka",
    "source": "www.daijiworld.com",
    "snippet": "A week-long training by Indian Navy's Advanced Light Helicopter (ALH) for training of Sri Lanka Air Force (SLAF) pilots and Sri Lanka Navy ships for shipborne helicopter operations is now being conducted,",
    "url": "https://www.daijiworld.com/news/newsDisplay?newsID=941582",
    "url_hash": "cec1270b2bd28b0105b9e0d30a0a40d0",
    "ut": 1648435949,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "week-long",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Indian Navy's",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Advanced Light Helicopter",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "ALH",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Air Force (SLAF",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Navy",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          30
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-28",
    "title": "HNB partners with OnePay expanding e-commerce solution for SME's",
    "source": "bizenglish.adaderana.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's leading private sector bank HNB PLC, partnered with popular internet payment gateway provider OnePay, further expanding the selection of online shopping options available to customers and its extensive portfolio of SMEs across the island.",
    "url": "http://bizenglish.adaderana.lk/hnb-partners-with-onepay-expanding-e-commerce-solution-for-smes/",
    "url_hash": "4aef262f4051d2059e8477cc9bc1850c",
    "ut": 1648436609,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "HNB PLC",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "OnePay",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]