[
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Following are the top foreign stories at 1700 hours",
    "source": "www.outlookindia.com",
    "snippet": "Modi to meet US Vice President Kamala Harris, hold bilaterals with Japanese and Australian PMs on Thursday Washington: Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Thursday is scheduled to have as many as eight meetings, including with Vice President Kamala Harris, on the first working day of his current US trip. By Lalit K Jha FGN20 G4-UNSC-REFORMS Indispensable to reform UN Security Council, make it more legitimate, representative: G4 nations New York: The G4 nations of India, Brazil, Germany and Japan have reaffirmed that it is \"indispensable\" to reform the Security Council through an expansion in permanent and non-permanent seats to enable the UN organ to better deal with the \"ever-complex and evolving challenges\" to the maintenance of international peace and security. By Yoshita Singh FGN28 US-HARRIS-MODI-MEETING-DIASPORA Kamala Harris meeting Modi is ''coming of age'' moment for Indian diaspora, says her home state newspaper Washington: US Vice President Kamala Harris meeting Prime Minister Narendra Modi in the White House on Thursday afternoon is a \"coming of age\" moment for the Indian diaspora, a prominent US newspaper in her home state has said on the eve of the historic meeting between the two leaders. By Lalit K Jha FGN35 UK-INDIA-TRAVEL-LD COVISHIELD Vaccine certification for travel must meet 'minimum criteria', says UK London: The UK government has said that COVID-19 vaccine certification from all countries must meet a \"minimum criteria\" and that it is working with India on a \"phased approach\" to its international travel norms. By Aditi Khanna FGN17 G20-JAISHANKAR-LD AFGHANISTAN Taliban's commitment not to allow use of Afghan soil for terrorism in any manner should be implemented: Jaishankar New York: External Affairs Minister S Jaishankar has told the G20 nations that the Taliban's commitment not to allow the use of Afghanistan's soil for terrorism in any manner should be implemented and the world expects a broad-based, inclusive process that involves representation from all sections of the Afghan society. By Yoshita Singh FGN25 US-MODI-LD DIASPORA Indian diaspora has distinguished itself across the world: Modi Washington: Prime Minister Narendra Modi has commended the Indian Diaspora for distinguishing itself across the world, as he received an enthusiastic welcome from the community on his arrival here on a major visit to further enhance Indo-US relations. By Lalit K Jha FGN15 US-MODI-CEOS Modi to interact with global CEOs to highlight opportunities in India Washington: Prime Minister Narendra Modi has said he would highlight economic opportunities in India during his meetings with CEOs here. By Lalit K Jha FGN27 US-AUKUS-LD INDIA US rules out adding India or Japan to security alliance with Australia and UK Washington: The US has ruled out adding India or Japan to the new trilateral security partnership with Australia and Britain to meet the challenges of the 21st century in the strategic Indo-Pacific region. By Lalit K Jha FGN29 UN-LANKA-RAJAPAKSA Meaningful reconciliation through domestic institutions is essential to achieve lasting peace: Rajapaksa United Nations: A meaningful reconciliation with the Tamil community through domestic institutions is essential to achieve lasting peace in Sri Lanka, President Gotabaya Rajapaksa has said and stressed that his government is ready to engage with all stakeholders and to obtain the support of its international partners in the process. By Yoshita Singh Taipei: Taiwan announced Thursday it has applied to join an 11-nation Pacific trade group, setting up a potential clash with rival Beijing over the status of the island democracy. (AP) FGN26 US-QURESHI-TALIBAN AP Interview: Top Pakistan diplomat details Taliban plan United Nations: Be realistic. Show patience. Engage. And above all, don''t isolate. Those are the pillars of an approach emerging in Pakistan to deal with the fledgling government that is suddenly running the country next door once again — Afghanistan''s resurgent, often-volatile Taliban. (AP) FGN11 VIRUS-UNGA-BIDEN Biden doubles US global donation of COVID-19 vaccine shots Washington: President Joe Biden has announced that the United States is doubling its purchase of Pfizer''s COVID-19 shots to share with the world to 1 billion doses as he embraces the goal of vaccinating 70 per cent of the global population within the next year. (AP) Outlook's annual ranking of India's top 21 Private Medical Universities in 2021 will help students make an informed choice. Outlook-ICARE India's Top Universities Rankings 2021: Top 15 Government Medical Universities Outlook's annual ranking of India's top 15 Government Medical Universities in 2021 will help students make an informed choice. Know what's behind the apparent and what doesn't show. Your journey into the myriad shades of truth with Outlook.",
    "url": "https://www.outlookindia.com/newsscroll/following-are-the-top-foreign-stories-at-1700-hours/2165509",
    "url_hash": "23bebf99fad3340495e6d1d867c62795",
    "ut": 1632442110,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kamala Harris",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Japanese",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Australian",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Thursday",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Washington",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Narendra Modi",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Thursday",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "as many as eight",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kamala Harris",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the first working day",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          48
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          51,
          52
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Lalit K Jha",
        "start_end": [
          55,
          58
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN Security Council",
        "start_end": [
          67,
          70
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "New York",
        "start_end": [
          80,
          82
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "G4",
        "start_end": [
          84,
          85
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          87,
          88
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Brazil",
        "start_end": [
          89,
          90
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Germany",
        "start_end": [
          91,
          92
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Japan",
        "start_end": [
          93,
          94
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Security Council",
        "start_end": [
          104,
          107
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN",
        "start_end": [
          120,
          121
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Yoshita",
        "start_end": [
          145,
          146
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Singh",
        "start_end": [
          146,
          147
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          148,
          149
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kamala Harris",
        "start_end": [
          157,
          159
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Modi",
        "start_end": [
          160,
          161
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Indian",
        "start_end": [
          169,
          170
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Washington",
        "start_end": [
          177,
          178
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          179,
          180
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kamala Harris",
        "start_end": [
          182,
          184
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Narendra Modi",
        "start_end": [
          187,
          189
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the White House",
        "start_end": [
          190,
          193
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Thursday",
        "start_end": [
          194,
          195
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "TIME",
        "text": "afternoon",
        "start_end": [
          195,
          196
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Indian",
        "start_end": [
          206,
          207
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          211,
          212
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          228,
          229
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Lalit K Jha",
        "start_end": [
          232,
          235
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "London",
        "start_end": [
          257,
          258
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "UK",
        "start_end": [
          260,
          261
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          284,
          285
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Aditi Khanna",
        "start_end": [
          298,
          300
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "G20-JAISHANKAR-LD",
        "start_end": [
          301,
          306
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Taliban",
        "start_end": [
          307,
          308
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Afghan",
        "start_end": [
          315,
          316
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Jaishankar New York",
        "start_end": [
          326,
          329
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "S Jaishankar",
        "start_end": [
          333,
          335
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "G20",
        "start_end": [
          338,
          339
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Taliban",
        "start_end": [
          342,
          343
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Afghanistan",
        "start_end": [
          351,
          352
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Afghan",
        "start_end": [
          381,
          382
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Yoshita Singh",
        "start_end": [
          385,
          387
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          388,
          389
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Indian diaspora",
        "start_end": [
          394,
          396
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Narendra Modi",
        "start_end": [
          408,
          410
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Indian",
        "start_end": [
          413,
          414
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Lalit K Jha",
        "start_end": [
          448,
          451
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          452,
          453
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          467,
          468
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Washington",
        "start_end": [
          468,
          469
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Narendra Modi",
        "start_end": [
          472,
          474
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          482,
          483
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Lalit K Jha",
        "start_end": [
          491,
          494
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          495,
          496
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          501,
          502
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          505,
          506
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Japan",
        "start_end": [
          507,
          508
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Australia",
        "start_end": [
          512,
          513
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "UK",
        "start_end": [
          514,
          515
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Washington",
        "start_end": [
          515,
          516
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          518,
          519
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          523,
          524
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Japan",
        "start_end": [
          525,
          526
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Australia",
        "start_end": [
          533,
          534
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Britain",
        "start_end": [
          535,
          536
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the 21st century",
        "start_end": [
          541,
          544
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Indo-Pacific",
        "start_end": [
          547,
          550
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Lalit K Jha",
        "start_end": [
          553,
          556
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN",
        "start_end": [
          557,
          558
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Rajapaksa United Nations",
        "start_end": [
          574,
          577
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Tamil",
        "start_end": [
          583,
          584
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          595,
          597
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gotabaya Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          599,
          601
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Yoshita",
        "start_end": [
          629,
          630
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Taipei",
        "start_end": [
          631,
          632
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Taiwan",
        "start_end": [
          633,
          634
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Thursday",
        "start_end": [
          635,
          636
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "11",
        "start_end": [
          642,
          643
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Pacific trade group",
        "start_end": [
          645,
          648
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Beijing",
        "start_end": [
          656,
          657
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "AP",
        "start_end": [
          666,
          667
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          669,
          670
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          678,
          679
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Taliban",
        "start_end": [
          681,
          682
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "United Nations",
        "start_end": [
          683,
          685
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Pakistan",
        "start_end": [
          710,
          711
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Afghanistan",
        "start_end": [
          728,
          729
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Taliban",
        "start_end": [
          736,
          737
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "AP",
        "start_end": [
          739,
          740
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "VIRUS",
        "start_end": [
          742,
          743
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          749,
          750
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Washington",
        "start_end": [
          756,
          757
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Joe Biden",
        "start_end": [
          759,
          761
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "the United States",
        "start_end": [
          764,
          767
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Pfizer",
        "start_end": [
          772,
          773
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "1 billion",
        "start_end": [
          783,
          785
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "70 per cent",
        "start_end": [
          793,
          796
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "the next year",
        "start_end": [
          801,
          804
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "AP",
        "start_end": [
          806,
          807
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Outlook",
        "start_end": [
          808,
          809
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "annual",
        "start_end": [
          810,
          811
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          813,
          814
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "21",
        "start_end": [
          816,
          817
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2021",
        "start_end": [
          821,
          822
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Outlook-ICARE India's",
        "start_end": [
          830,
          835
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Top Universities Rankings",
        "start_end": [
          835,
          838
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2021",
        "start_end": [
          838,
          839
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "15",
        "start_end": [
          841,
          842
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Universities Outlook's",
        "start_end": [
          844,
          847
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "annual",
        "start_end": [
          847,
          848
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          850,
          851
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "15",
        "start_end": [
          853,
          854
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2021",
        "start_end": [
          858,
          859
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PRODUCT",
        "text": "Outlook",
        "start_end": [
          888,
          889
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Suspended Sri Lankan players may return to competitive cricket",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "There is a possibility of the domestic ban imposed on Sri Lankan cricketers Kusal Mendis, Niroshan Dickwella and Danushka Gunathilaka being lifted, provided they show progressive reports on the mandatory counselling they have been asked to undergo.",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/suspended-sri-lankan-players-may-return-to-competitive-cricket/",
    "url_hash": "3397753f829955375b2eae3e7f5c1d7b",
    "ut": 1632442571,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kusal Mendis",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Niroshan Dickwella",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Danushka Gunathilaka",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Domestic cricket to commence on Oct. 20",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Cricket (SLC) is set to commence the domestic season of 2021/2022 from October 20. According to a senior official of SLC, they have instructed clubs to start their preparations, adhering to the health guidelines issued by the government,",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/domestic-cricket-to-commence-on-oct-20/",
    "url_hash": "b6ccc6689b24ae32449b861f346f5ae4",
    "ut": 1632443359,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Cricket",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "2021/2022",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "October 20",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "SLC",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Physical location and 'jurisdictional location' are separate matters",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "In what should have been a pedestrian application in the District Court, which should have been decided on the bare facts, a District Judge made a wrong decision about the jurisdiction of the court with regard to a certain defendant,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/physical-location-and-jurisdictional-location-are-separate-matters/ar-AAOL9PZ",
    "url_hash": "7dd3a2dab87c2a1a94ced84271ec109b",
    "ut": 1632443388,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the District Court",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          12
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Sri Lanka should open schools, but reduce exam pressure: EducationForumSL",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka should open schools as soon as it is safe to do so, but students should not be subject to the same exam pressure as earlier, which is in case a flawed approach that leaves students without reasoning skills,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-should-open-schools-but-reduce-exam-pressure-educationforumsl-86432/",
    "url_hash": "9beded3408ece84ebd31d82eed5216b7",
    "ut": 1632443499,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "SL begin World Cup preparations today",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Rex Clementine Sri Lanka's cricketers who are in a bio-secure bubble at the Cinnamon Grand in Colombo will end their three day quarantine today and will start group training. Following the group training,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sl-begin-world-cup-preparations-today/",
    "url_hash": "5239492ee611a9a0e489db216e5ad9ff",
    "ut": 1632443719,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Cinnamon Grand",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "three day",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "today",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "As youngsters refuse vaccines; Medics warn Sri Lanka's immunization programme at risk",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "As health authorities come under severe pressure due to the lack of interest among youngsters to get the COVID-19 vaccines, medical workers yesterday warned that Sri Lanka's immunization programme will come at risk if youngsters have no confidence on all vaccinations.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/top_story/As-youngsters-refuse-vaccines-Medics-warn-Sri-Lankas-immunization-programme-at-risk/155-221027",
    "url_hash": "69de4d8e3fc447130a4107bfb11ab7e2",
    "ut": 1632449300,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          29
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Sri Lanka latest import restrictions should be revisited: Jayasundara",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka central bank's recent import restrictions over 600 items should be revisited as it is hindering a booming service exports of information technology (IT), president's secretary P B Jayasundera said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-latest-import-restrictions-should-be-revisited-jayasundara-86434/",
    "url_hash": "33eb6267e9e4fb9a8344e916d908c779",
    "ut": 1632449329,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "600",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "B Jayasundera",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Sri Lanka Athletics gives priority to Asian Games",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Reemus Fernando  Sri Lanka Athletics will give priority to Asian Games over the Commonwealth Games as the two major sports events take place within five weeks from each other in 2022. The track and field governing body indicated their priorities at a meeting with the National Olympic Committee yesterday.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-athletics-gives-priority-to-asian-games/",
    "url_hash": "6ec9d1da56b60afe663747999fdd6805",
    "ut": 1632451710,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Reemus Fernando  Sri Lanka Athletics",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Asian Games",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Commonwealth Games",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "five weeks",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2022",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the National Olympic Committee",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          50
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          50,
          51
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-24",
    "title": "Public Security Minister: Terrorists still at large pose threat to Sri Lanka",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sarath Weerasekera told Parliament on Wednesday (22) that Sri Lanka would be under threat as long as the IS ideology promising 72 virgins in paradise for those who sacrificed their lives in the name of Jihad existed.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/public-security-minister-terrorists-still-at-large-pose-threat-to-sri-lanka/",
    "url_hash": "a90da8ca9b9c1ee2ebb375b1252d5e09",
    "ut": 1632451918,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sarath Weerasekera",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Parliament",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          5,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "22",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "72",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Jihad",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          38
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]