[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Punchihewa's new book on King Vijayabahu, the redeemer of Lanka",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "After becoming the ruler of the island, he wanted to bring about economic ... it may mot be wrong to say that King Vijayabahu wass the greatest ruler of Sri Lanka. In enumerating his virtues, a recent researcher scholar said, \"If there is a Sri Lankan ...",
    "url": "https://island.lk/punchihewas-new-book-on-king-vijayabahu-the-redeemer-of-lanka/",
    "url_hash": "76bf7d0af5cbafe88d62b99046e276ba",
    "ut": 1648339271,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "King Vijayabahu",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          51
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "More on wrecks and treasure of the sea off Galle",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sixty years or so later I was in Galle, organizing an international group of maritime archaeologists who were training a clutch of our young archaeology undergraduates and, at the same time, compiling a data base of shipwrecks in Galle Bay.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/more-on-wrecks-and-treasure-of-the-sea-off-galle/",
    "url_hash": "3468e88812cec183c2abd5f51158d10f",
    "ut": 1648339946,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sixty years or so later",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Galle",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Galle Bay",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          43
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Lanka should set up a currency board to stop rupee depreciation: US economist",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka should set up a currency board to stop further currency falls, US economist Steve Hanke has said as the island's currency collapsed from 203 to 290 to the US dollar in an attempt to float the currency which has not yet succeeded.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/lanka-should-set-up-a-currency-board-to-stop-rupee-depreciation-us-economist/",
    "url_hash": "2203d920e2a94f288719286fff09f41d",
    "ut": 1648339950,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Steve Hanke",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "203",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "290",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "US",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "S Jaishankar To Visit Sri Lanka Next Week To Hold Bilateral Talks, Attend BIMSTEC Engagements",
    "source": "www.outlookindia.com",
    "snippet": "This will be S Jaishankar's first visit to the island nation since India extended an economic relief package to bail Sri Lanka out of the current economic crisis.",
    "url": "https://www.outlookindia.com/international/s-jaishankar-to-visit-sri-lanka-next-week-to-hold-bilateral-talks-attend-bimstec-engagements-news-188687",
    "url_hash": "4ed47b45e20c4fe4657c5e2a053c042b",
    "ut": 1648341397,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "S Jaishankar's",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "first",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          23
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Sri Lanka, short of food, faces an economic crisis",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Although the earth is bountiful in Sri Lanka, which was formerly Ceylon, the nation of 13 million has a critical food shortage. Moreover, it is going broke, jolted by inflation, torn by internal dissension and plainly alarmed about the future.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220327/sunday-times-2/sri-lanka-short-of-food-faces-an-economic-crisis-478021.html",
    "url_hash": "d3bab76832cddb0b604197a8fd893b8c",
    "ut": 1648342657,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "13 million",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Learning about the past from the map makers of history",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Bellin's map of Ceylon was originally published in 1764 and is now a rare collector's item. He also published in 1754, a plan of Galle Fort and a sketch of it as seen from the sea. Bellin's copper engraved map of the Maldives,",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220327/plus/learning-about-the-past-from-the-map-makers-of-history-477728.html",
    "url_hash": "97f809d5c3987417e7f31a42cb3ece44",
    "ut": 1648342671,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Bellin",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Ceylon",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "1764",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "1754",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "Galle Fort",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Bellin",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Maldives",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          49
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Freedom of movement guaranteed",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "No fuel price hike can curtail your freedom of movement if you have a bicycle. A tourist in bicycle is seen passing by the latest tourist attraction — street protests — outside the Fort railway station on Friday.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220327/news/freedom-of-movement-guaranteed-478270.html",
    "url_hash": "30e36e718e775d4e641a4de5e37dfb48",
    "ut": 1648342671,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Fort",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Friday",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-27",
    "title": "Bringing her fearless murals to Colombo",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "I paint huge murals on the street that are often 60 feet high and 60 feet wide while I'm hanging off a six-storey building in the freezing cold with a huge brush in my hand,\" Shilo Shiv Suleman describes a typical day as she takes to the streets to create bold and colourful murals centred on marginalised communities around the world.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220327/plus/bringing-her-fearless-murals-to-colombo-477751.html",
    "url_hash": "56b723c719e5d100c73cdc2ca900105b",
    "ut": 1648343346,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "QUANTITY",
        "text": "60 feet",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "QUANTITY",
        "text": "60 feet",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "six",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]