[
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Top panel sounds alarm, insists it's time for urgent economic reforms",
    "source": "www.ft.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka facing one of the worst economic crises in its history ... 'A Framework for Economic Recovery'. Advocata is a Colombo-based think tank. Providing a breakdown of the economic challenges before the economy, in her presentation Dr. Perera ...",
    "url": "https://www.ft.lk/front-page/Top-panel-sounds-alarm-insists-it-s-time-for-urgent-economic-reforms/44-723143",
    "url_hash": "a464cac1410879a41434f61a9701dc3e",
    "ut": 1631750652,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Perera",
        "start_end": [
          45,
          46
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Hindi Diwas celebrations in Sri Lanka",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "In commemoration of the Hindi Diwas on September 14, 2021, the Swami Vivekananda Cultural Centre (SVCC), the cultural arm of the High Commission of India, organised a series of events and competitions.",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/hindi-diwas-celebrations-in-sri-lanka/ar-AAOuC2q",
    "url_hash": "cd92580dde4c71d3db5cd490422ab8fe",
    "ut": 1631750891,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Hindi Diwas",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "September 14, 2021",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Swami Vivekananda Cultural Centre",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the High Commission of India",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          30
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Sri Lanka skipper rues preparing spinning tracks for T20I series against South Africa",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "White ball skipper Dasun Shanaka said that had Sri Lanka prepared good wickets for the T20I series against South Africa his team could have performed much better.",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/featured/lankan-skipper-rues-preparing-spinning-tracks-for-t20i-series/",
    "url_hash": "ccb44c5ee97f63d0f7fb44d1f8207d0e",
    "ut": 1631750891,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "South Africa",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Are the Americans and their Acolytes Attempting to Frogmarch Mahinda to Walk the Plank?",
    "source": "www.lankaweb.com",
    "snippet": "There is not a sausage the Americans can do with it and the Global South, which foresaw the dangers of the American conspiracy, do not give a tuppeny damn to the defanged outcome, Resolution 46/1. But during the process America deviously budgeted a sum of 2 million USD for the establishment of this investigative and prosecuting mechanism,",
    "url": "http://www.lankaweb.com/news/items/2021/09/15/are-the-americans-and-their-acolytes-attempting-to-frogmarch-mahinda-to-walk-the-plank/",
    "url_hash": "2cd127b350a0f78dfa3d6110e5ccf149",
    "ut": 1631750891,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Americans",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Global South",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          15
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "American",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          23
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LAW",
        "text": "Resolution 46/1",
        "start_end": [
          36,
          38
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "America",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "2 million",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          51
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "ERASING THE EELAM VICTORY Part 19C",
    "source": "www.lankaweb.com",
    "snippet": "The Tamil Separatist Movement was not crushed by the Eelam defeat. They knew it was going to happen and were ready for it. The Movement created two new organizations after the war ended, 'Transitional government of Tamil Eelam'(TGTE) and the 'Global TamilForum' (GTF).",
    "url": "http://www.lankaweb.com/news/items/2021/09/15/erasing-the-eelam-victory-part-19c/",
    "url_hash": "91ea8e8f388397b176018e9c5cb5c9e1",
    "ut": 1631751556,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Tamil Separatist Movement",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Eelam",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "two",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Tamil Eelam'(TGTE",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          42
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PRODUCT",
        "text": "Global TamilForum'",
        "start_end": [
          46,
          49
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "No ban on eco-friendly food packages - Minister",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "Environment Minister Mahinda Amaraweera said that the Central Environmental Authority (CEA) had informed him that the eco-friendly food package introduced by Tharushi Vidushika Rajapaksa, a resident of Ratnapura who is studying at the University of Colombo,",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/srilanka/no-ban-on-eco-friendly-food-packages-minister/ar-AAOuvbP",
    "url_hash": "04ca6b688f42c4132c84ac7f475ed59f",
    "ut": 1631751580,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Mahinda Amaraweera",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Central Environmental Authority",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "CEA",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Tharushi Vidushika Rajapaksa",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Ratnapura",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the University of Colombo",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Crisis-hit Sri Lanka hopes to boost foreign inflows through remittances, tourism, high investments",
    "source": "www.southasiamonitor.org",
    "snippet": "In a bid to boost foreign inflows, crisis-hit Sri Lanka is banking on high investments, remittances, and tourist arrivals, Cabinet Co-spokesman Minister Ramesh Pathirana said as imports hit a 17-month high in July,",
    "url": "https://www.southasiamonitor.org/index.php/sri-lanka/crisis-hit-sri-lanka-hopes-boost-foreign-inflows-through-remittances-tourism-high",
    "url_hash": "55e25c0b4cf9398cd261cceaa6a512d9",
    "ut": 1631754250,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Cabinet Co-spokesman",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Ramesh Pathirana",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "17-month",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          40
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "July",
        "start_end": [
          42,
          43
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "World leaders face new rule at UN meeting",
    "source": "www.hirunews.lk",
    "snippet": "World leaders will have to be vaccinated against the coronavirus to speak at the U.N. General Assembly's big meeting next week, the assembly leader and New York City officials have said, prompting swift objections from at least one nation.",
    "url": "https://www.hirunews.lk/english/282314/world-leaders-face-new-rule-at-un-meeting",
    "url_hash": "f172cb0c430f493c4c8f7475883d71f9",
    "ut": 1631754499,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the U.N. General Assembly's",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "next week",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "New York City",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "at least one",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          41
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Moderna says COVID-19 vaccine protection wanes, makes case for booster",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "New data from Moderna Inc's (MRNA.O) large COVID-19 vaccine trial shows that the protection it offers wanes over time, supporting the case for booster doses, the company said in a news release on Wednesday.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Moderna-says-COVID-19-vaccine-protection-wanes-makes-case-for-booster/108-220477",
    "url_hash": "69f522632416909af6ddf72b9042af01",
    "ut": 1631755146,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Moderna Inc's",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Can a new scheme help stop abuse of Singapore's domestic workers?",
    "source": "www.aljazeera.com",
    "snippet": "Migrants working as household cleaners enjoy better conditions than the city-state's legion of live-in domestic workers.",
    "url": "https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/9/16/can-a-new-scheme-clean-up-singapores-home-help-industry",
    "url_hash": "7e336d2c745d86fa08b98042387a9289",
    "ut": 1631755756,
    "ent_info_list": []
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Anil's Ghost",
    "source": "www.abebooks.co.uk",
    "snippet": "Although Anil's Ghost is a poetic and beautifully written book, it is also a tough, uncompromising and brave novel about a terrifying conflict that the world has chosen to ignore. --Jerry Brotton",
    "url": "https://www.abebooks.co.uk/products/isbn/9780747548652",
    "url_hash": "d0e6a0b42835edbe1b35440cf7940e3f",
    "ut": 1631757496,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Anil",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Brotton",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "Press Release: Fitch Rtgs: Sri Lankan FLCs Face Challenges Beyond the Covid-19 Pandemic",
    "source": "www.sharecast.com",
    "snippet": "Fitch Ratings-Colombo-15 September 2021: Restrictions on vehicle importation will continue to constrain growth prospects of Sri Lankan finance and leasing companies (FLCs), dampening prospects for the sector's earnings,",
    "url": "https://www.sharecast.com/news/market_reports/press-release-fitch-rtgs-sri-lankan-flcs-face-challenges-beyond-the-covid-19-pandemic--8095582.html",
    "url_hash": "a69e52cd0262e737f3fa5157b29a5599",
    "ut": 1631758116,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Fitch Ratings-Colombo-15",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "September 2021",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-16",
    "title": "How Sri Lanka's IMF-backed 'Young Plan' led to a foreign debt death spiral",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "While Sri Lanka's monetary meltdown acceleration with historic low interest rates driven by money printing after the tax cuts of 2019, the storm gathered pace from 2015, when rapid foreign debt accumulation greater than the annual foreign financed deficits began.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/how-sri-lankas-imf-backed-young-plan-led-to-a-foreign-debt-death-spiral-86206/",
    "url_hash": "d49ad985e4d6cf483ca17eb802316784",
    "ut": 1631758588,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2019",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2015",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          29
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "annual",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]