[
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Listen to medical experts at least now: JVP urges Govt.",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Government should at least now pay heed to the recommendations and guidance of medical experts and specialists in the effort to combat the Covid pandemic, as the only way forward in economic and social aspects was to get rid of the pandemic as soon as possible,",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Listen-to-medical-experts-at-least-now-JVP-urges-Govt/108-220313",
    "url_hash": "5db00cb193c729a38abd8c84d4dd90a0",
    "ut": 1631578094,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Covid",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka BOP deficit soars to US$2.7bn to July 2021 as bond auctions fail",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has run a balance of payments deficit of 2.755 billion US dollars up to July 2021, official data show, a record high, as historically high levels of liquidity was injected to expand unsustainable credit,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-bop-deficit-soars-to-us2-7bn-to-july-2021-as-bond-auctions-fail-86094/",
    "url_hash": "7d18a37ebfb51fb2853364ab45316e76",
    "ut": 1631578553,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "2.755 billion US dollars",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "July 2021",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Is it business as usual in 2005?",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Can you get back to business as usual because your life and limbs, your loved ones and your property are all safe? No. The tsunami has wiped away more than life and property in coastal and low-lying areas.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/050109/ft/@home.html",
    "url_hash": "689f0b4e186daa0a37eac98040b3fdd7",
    "ut": 1631579965,
    "ent_info_list": []
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka BOP deficit soars to US$2.7bn up to July as bond auctions fail",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has run a balance of payments deficit of 2.755 billion US dollars up to July 2021, official data show, a record high, as historically high levels of liquidity was injected to expand unsustainable credit,",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-bop-deficit-soars-to-us2-7bn-up-to-july-as-bond-auctions-fail-86094/",
    "url_hash": "ed8990c0cf87e56b64d19bef8f9322b5",
    "ut": 1631580149,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "2.755 billion US dollars",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "July 2021",
        "start_end": [
          16,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Post-covid clinics for those with health issues after recovery: Medical specialist",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Claiming that some people who recover from Covid-19 could experience post-covid symptoms such as cough, breathing difficulties and chest pain even after two weeks of recovery, a medical specialist said yesterday such people should seek medical advice.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/breaking_news/Post-covid-clinics-for-those-with-health-issues-after-recovery-Medical-specialist/108-220308",
    "url_hash": "7c60e2316b269d03cffc8c52bae8ba86",
    "ut": 1631581693,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "two weeks",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Deletion of computer database of NMRA could be an act of drug mafia: AG",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Attorney General yesterday informed Colombo Chief Magistrate's Court that deletion of the computer database of the National Medicines Regulatory Authority (NMRA) could be an act of drug smugglers.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Deletion-of-computer-database-of-NMRA-could-be-an-act-of-drug-mafia-AG/342-220310",
    "url_hash": "d7197769989b1013f2a11b8ef6341673",
    "ut": 1631581694,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          3,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the National Medicines Regulatory Authority",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Keep training uninterrupted, the biggest challenge for athletes in centenary year",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka Athletics announces calendar for 2022 by Reemus Fernando How to keep training uninterrupted amidst the Covid-19 pandemic to succeed at international events is the biggest problem the track and field athletes need to find answers to in the sport's centenary year in 2022 as Sri Lanka Athletics announced a busy 2022 Competition calendar",
    "url": "https://island.lk/keep-training-uninterrupted-the-biggest-challenge-for-athletes-in-centenary-year/",
    "url_hash": "d57cb93e0ef6391b5f86af053cf91ed8",
    "ut": 1631582233,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Athletics",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2022",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Reemus Fernando",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2022",
        "start_end": [
          45,
          46
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lanka Athletics",
        "start_end": [
          47,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Allianz Lanka wins Claims Initiative of the Year",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Allianz Insurance Lanka Ltd received the prestigious 'Claims Initiative of the Year - Sri Lanka' award at the Insurance Asia Awards 2021 held recently. Organized by Insurance Asia, a renowned publication devoted to insurance companies,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/allianz-lanka-wins-claims-initiative-of-the-year/",
    "url_hash": "f1e950dd9d9ce89caea765da29f659ea",
    "ut": 1631583274,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Allianz Insurance Lanka Ltd",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "EVENT",
        "text": "the Year - Sri Lanka'",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "FAC",
        "text": "the Insurance Asia Awards 2021",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          24
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Insurance Asia",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Concerns over civil society engagement with government",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "By Jehan Perera The 48th session of the UN Human Rights Council that started this week in Geneva will not be having any new UN resolutions with regard to Sri Lanka. This session will only see the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights,",
    "url": "https://island.lk/concerns-over-civil-society-engagement-with-government/",
    "url_hash": "8ee37ac0f80a07441c1ca7b7a65d59e2",
    "ut": 1631583303,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Jehan Perera",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORDINAL",
        "text": "48th",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the UN Human Rights Council",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "this week",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Geneva",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UN",
        "start_end": [
          38,
          39
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka seek batting stability in dead rubber",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Rex Clementine After a hard fought win in the ODI series, old problems have resurfaced for Sri Lanka in T20 cricket as the team is unable to bat out the 20 overs. Sri Lanka handed the T20 series to the Proteas on Sunday after suffering a heavy nine wicket defeat with 35 balls to",
    "url": "https://island.lk/sri-lanka-seek-batting-stability-in-dead-rubber/",
    "url_hash": "783ab979742b3c906769798d75726e6a",
    "ut": 1631584054,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "ODI",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          10
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "20",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          36
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "the Proteas on",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          44
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Sunday",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          45
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "nine",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          50
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "35",
        "start_end": [
          53,
          54
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Easter Sunday attack: Trial-at-bar bench to hear cases on October 4",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The Colombo High Court Trial-at-bar has fixed for October 4, to hear the cases filed against 25 accused including Naufer Moulavi in connection with the Easter Sunday Terrorist attacks. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Easter-Sunday-attack-Trial-at-bar-bench-to-hear-cases-on-October-4/342-220311",
    "url_hash": "5eab0b2a4b811f966e082df5b5161f3e",
    "ut": 1631585294,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "October 4",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "25",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Naufer Moulavi",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Easter Sunday Terrorist",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          33
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "UNP seeks donations from China",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "UNP Chairman Vajira Abeywardene yesterday said leader of his party Ranil Wickremesinghe had requested for Chinese assistance to fight the COVID- 19 pandemic. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/UNP-seeks-donations-from-China/342-220312",
    "url_hash": "a293b6983980fd72f434fd359953066d",
    "ut": 1631585294,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UNP",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Vajira Abeywardene",
        "start_end": [
          2,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Ranil Wickremesinghe",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Chinese",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "19",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Explained: Sri Lanka's economic crisis",
    "source": "www.theweek.in",
    "snippet": "As rating agencies slashed their estimates for Sri Lanka, food lines formed across the country, and a balance of payments crisis threatened to implode the economy, Sri Lanka's government officials denied the existence of a food crisis in the country.",
    "url": "https://www.theweek.in/news/world/2021/09/13/explained-sri-lankas-economic-crisis.html",
    "url_hash": "f84fc624f8cee830d384fea197274da9",
    "ut": 1631587642,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          32
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Post-covid clinics for those with health issues after recovery: Medical specialist",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "Claiming that some people who recover from Covid-19 could experience post-covid symptoms such as cough, breathing difficulties and chest pain even after two weeks of recovery, a medical specialist said yesterday such people should seek medical advice.",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Post-covid-clinics-for-those-with-health-issues-after-recovery-Medical-specialist/342-220308",
    "url_hash": "ddd8cd83ccd4728f99087fbe258397f5",
    "ut": 1631588894,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "two weeks",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          34,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Cash deposit margin on mobile phones, computers: Ruwan asks for decision to be revised",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The 100 percent cash deposit for importation of items such as computers and mobile phones should be reversed as they are essential for school Children, UNP Deputy Leader Ruwan Wijewardene said yesterday. Mr. Wijewardene who was speaking at a zoom meeting ...",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Cash-deposit-margin-on-mobile-phones-computers-Ruwan-asks-for-decision-to-be-revised/342-220309",
    "url_hash": "1adfaac6a2cb088850a1c2375cc6e986",
    "ut": 1631588894,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERCENT",
        "text": "100 percent",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Children",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "UNP",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          27
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Ruwan Wijewardene",
        "start_end": [
          29,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "yesterday",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Wijewardene",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          36
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka recovery framework launched by Advocata Institute at 3.30pm",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "A recovery framework for Sri Lanka will be launched by Advocata Institute, a Colombo-based think tank, backed by a panel of economists.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-recovery-framework-launched-by-advocata-institute-at-3-30pm-86107/",
    "url_hash": "c03e0f61bc3fb7be0af8169f87004dbd",
    "ut": 1631588919,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Advocata Institute",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Which batter has the biggest difference between averages in wins and defeats in Tests?",
    "source": "africa.espn.com",
    "snippet": "And what's the record for the most consecutive Test appearances by a player against the same opposition? | ESPN.com",
    "url": "https://africa.espn.com/cricket/story/_/id/32205861/ask-steven-which-batter-biggest-difference-averages-wins-defeats-tests",
    "url_hash": "6908bf62afc4d29b244593315de53235",
    "ut": 1631589108,
    "ent_info_list": []
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "GSMB refutes claims that sand was exported to form an island in Maldives",
    "source": "www.hirunews.lk",
    "snippet": "The Geological Survey and Mines Bureau says that reports that Sri Lanka is preparing to export sea sand to form an island in the Maldives are false. In a statement, Bureau Director-General Engineer Sajjana de Silva said that a Sri Lankan construction company in the Maldives had exported the required amount of mineral sand.",
    "url": "https://www.hirunews.lk/english/282151/gsmb-refutes-claims-that-sand-was-exported-to-form-an-island-in-maldives",
    "url_hash": "48a44de07dc55c531855dcb8bf1b3d9e",
    "ut": 1631589683,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Geological",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Mines Bureau",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Maldives",
        "start_end": [
          24,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Bureau",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sajjana de Silva",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          40
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          43,
          45
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Maldives",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka Central Bank Veteran Cabraal Returns Amid Forex Crunch",
    "source": "www.bloombergquint.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka is turning to a veteran central banker as it seeks to bolster depleted foreign exchange reserves and service debt without seeking an international bailout. Ajith Nivard Cabraal, a former junior minister overseeing capital markets who led the Central Bank of Sri Lanka from 2006 until early 2015,",
    "url": "https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/sri-lanka-central-bank-veteran-cabraal-returns-amid-forex-crunch",
    "url_hash": "5e57b6dad73ea034bfa18976a92e5144",
    "ut": 1631590223,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Nivard Cabraal",
        "start_end": [
          28,
          30
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Central Bank of Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          40,
          46
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2006",
        "start_end": [
          47,
          48
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "early 2015",
        "start_end": [
          49,
          51
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "INTERVIEW: Amid disease and destruction, new UN Assembly president highlights hope",
    "source": "www.entornointeligente.com",
    "snippet": "Entornointeligente.com / The incoming President of the General Assembly says that hope is desperately needed for those billions around the world struggling with the COVID-19 pandemic, devastation, and strife.",
    "url": "https://www.entornointeligente.com/13/09/2021/interview-amid-disease-and-destruction-new-un-assembly-president-highlights-hope/",
    "url_hash": "a73bc184eb29b9a15c1da849eb2f08de",
    "ut": 1631590223,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Entornointeligente.com",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the General Assembly",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "CARDINAL",
        "text": "billions",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          18
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2021-09-14",
    "title": "Sri Lanka: Ajith Nivard Cabraal set to become the new Central Bank Governor",
    "source": "www.wionews.com",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka's former Finance Minister Ajith Nivard Cabraal is set to become the new Central Bank Governor in Sri Lanka. This comes after the former Governor resigned as the island nation now faces a deepening financial crisis.",
    "url": "https://www.wionews.com/videos/sri-lanka-ajith-nivard-cabraal-set-to-become-the-new-central-bank-governor-412909",
    "url_hash": "4fd5a40b960938ddee6bd99712d41ac3",
    "ut": 1631591123,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Finance",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Ajith Nivard",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          8
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Central Bank",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]