[
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "'Heart aches': Liz Hurley's sad reveal before Shane Warne's funeral",
    "source": "au.sports.yahoo.com",
    "snippet": "Liz Hurley has delivered a heartbreaking message on the eve of cricket legend Shane Warne's private funeral after not being able to attend the service. Hurley was engaged with Warne in 2013 and has expressed her devastation upon hearing of the cricket legend's death on March 4.",
    "url": "https://au.sports.yahoo.com/shane-warne-2022-liz-hurleys-devastating-reveal-before-funeral-000154357.html",
    "url_hash": "4a0ea65d68a9e2b9914664912bff9c06",
    "ut": 1647734480,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Liz Hurley",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Shane Warne's",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Hurley",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Warne",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2013",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "March 4",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Lanka in moment of crisis with great potential for change: senior political scientist",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Sri Lanka has reached a moment of crisis with a great deal of potential for change, and the conditions for significant change are rife except for leadership, senior political scientist Prof Jayadeva Uyangoda said.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/lanka-in-moment-of-crisis-with-great-potential-for-change-senior-political-scientist/",
    "url_hash": "128c6beeacf7988142b8ccd33b9bb790",
    "ut": 1647734916,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Jayadeva Uyangoda",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          35
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Jungles, ruins and shipwrecks",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "Somasiri Devendra Jungles fascinate me. It was a fascination that had been kindled by my father, as well as John Still, both of whom were archaeologists and writers. But, somehow, I never became one who trod the forest ways regularly.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/jungles-ruins-and-shipwrecks/",
    "url_hash": "23907b69484942fed64357ac684efb36",
    "ut": 1647735032,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Somasiri Devendra Jungles",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "John Still",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          23
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "IMF to begin talks with Lanka",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "The International Monetary Fund intends to begin discussions with Sri Lanka on a program to support the country, spokesman Gerry Rice said as the island is facing steep currency depreciation and inflation after an unusual bout of money printing to keep interest rates low.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/imf-to-begin-talks-with-lanka/",
    "url_hash": "9684881e82fceba832f4bb12eb0c564e",
    "ut": 1647735096,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Gerry Rice",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          22
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Lifetime Achievement Awards at Journalism Awards for Excellence 2019 & 2020",
    "source": "island.lk",
    "snippet": "The 19th and 20th Editions of the Journalism Awards for Excellence programme will culminate with the presentation of Awards on Tuesday, March 22, 2022 at the 'Blue', Colombo Hilton Hotel. The annual Awards Night for the years 2020 and 2021 had to be postponed due to the prevailing COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "url": "https://island.lk/lifetime-achievement-awards-at-journalism-awards-for-excellence-2019-2020/",
    "url_hash": "3a3697582ee786a3c75eb28d067c8b1e",
    "ut": 1647735148,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "LAW",
        "text": "the Journalism Awards for Excellence",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Tuesday, March 22, 2022",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Colombo Hilton Hotel",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          35
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
        "text": "annual Awards Night",
        "start_end": [
          37,
          40
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "'Heart aches': Liz Hurley's sad reveal before Shane Warne's funeral",
    "source": "nz.news.yahoo.com",
    "snippet": "Liz Hurley has delivered a heartbreaking message on the eve of cricket legend Shane Warne's private funeral after not being able to attend the service. Hurley was engaged with Warne in 2013 and has expressed her devastation upon hearing of the cricket legend's death on March 4.",
    "url": "https://nz.news.yahoo.com/shane-warne-2022-liz-hurleys-devastating-reveal-before-funeral-000154357.html",
    "url_hash": "974e7ce2d2c4fb2b247ff331dcffdbe7",
    "ut": 1647735908,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Liz Hurley",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Shane Warne's",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Hurley",
        "start_end": [
          27,
          28
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Warne",
        "start_end": [
          31,
          32
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "2013",
        "start_end": [
          33,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "March 4",
        "start_end": [
          48,
          50
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Colombo-based Western diplomats urge Sri Lanka to support Ukraine",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "As the oldest surviving democracy in Asia, history will judge Sri Lanka's stand of the 'middle path' on the Eastern European conflict. The conflict saw Russia invading Ukraine-a sovereign, democratic nation represented at the United Nations.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/columns/colombo-based-western-diplomats-urge-sri-lanka-to-support-ukraine-477320.html",
    "url_hash": "f9f307f7c02523440fda0f44a90a2f87",
    "ut": 1647737850,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Asia",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          11,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Eastern European",
        "start_end": [
          23,
          25
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Russia",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          33
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the United Nations",
        "start_end": [
          41,
          44
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "NDBIB and CT CLSA in strategic partnership",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Ltd (CT CLSA) have entered into a Collaboration Agreement to work together in raising capital for Sri Lankan corporates via Equity Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) on the Colombo Stock Exchange. A Collaboration Agreement setting out the framework for cooperation under this strategic alliance was signed on Wednesday,",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/business-times/ndbib-and-ct-clsa-in-strategic-partnership-476770.html",
    "url_hash": "9b2a4dd774fcc2f9f241b34e0fc8143b",
    "ut": 1647737970,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "EVENT",
        "text": "a Collaboration Agreement",
        "start_end": [
          8,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sri Lankan",
        "start_end": [
          18,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Equity Initial Public Offerings",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          26
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Colombo Stock Exchange",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          34
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "Wednesday",
        "start_end": [
          51,
          52
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "A nation of that fell upon their collective swords",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Pollard may have been better served by titling her writing, 'How Sri Lanka's Greedy and Incompetent Politicians of all Shades Destroyed a State' or more to the purpose, 'How a Nation of Fools Continually Elected Worse Fools to Fool Them - And Fell Upon Their Collective Swords.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/columns/a-nation-of-that-fell-upon-their-collective-swords-477175.html",
    "url_hash": "a7f30c31d4ea8deb19f4646a80f0dab3",
    "ut": 1647738183,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "State",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          26
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Defence headquarters building complex consultancy fees skyrockets",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Over 60 per cent of the construction work of Sri Lanka's Pentagon-styled Defence headquarters building complex at Akuregoda, Battaramulla has been completed amidst the rise in consultancy fees and building material costs,",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/business-times/defence-headquarters-building-complex-consultancy-fees-skyrockets-476764.html",
    "url_hash": "046b5a59d8d1f791afc6abe61b13237f",
    "ut": 1647738256,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "MONEY",
        "text": "60 per cent",
        "start_end": [
          1,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          9,
          12
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Pentagon",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          13
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Defence",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          16
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Akuregoda",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "IUSF calls off satyagraha campaign near Colombo-Fort railway station",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "The Inter-University Students Federation (IUSF) has given a further period to the Government to resolve a string of education related issues and have called off a satyagraha campaign opposite the Colombo-Fort railway station.",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/education/iusf-calls-off-satyagraha-campaign-near-colombo-fort-railway-station-477030.html",
    "url_hash": "db4799b05fd7db3917d5d9e424b40917",
    "ut": 1647738376,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The Inter-University Students Federation",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          6
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Australian mining company halts mineral explorations in Mannar",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "Australian mining company, Titanium Sands Ltd, currently carrying out extensive Ilmenite sand mining with a licence obtained in an allegedly irregular way on Mannar Island has decided to halt operations,",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/business-times/australian-mining-company-halts-mineral-explorations-in-mannar-476734.html",
    "url_hash": "2d3d9939536eb3ce611fdabeed53fa01",
    "ut": 1647738723,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "NORP",
        "text": "Australian",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Titanium Sands Ltd",
        "start_end": [
          4,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "LOC",
        "text": "Mannar Island",
        "start_end": [
          25,
          27
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "IMF urges Sri Lanka to restore macroeconomic stability",
    "source": "www.sundaytimes.lk",
    "snippet": "The International Monetary Fund (IMF) has emphasised the urgent need for Sri Lanka to implement a credible and coherent strategy to restore macroeconomic stability and debt sustainability, while protecting vulnerable groups through strengthened,",
    "url": "https://www.sundaytimes.lk/220320/business-times/imf-urges-sri-lanka-to-restore-macroeconomic-stability-476811.html",
    "url_hash": "c5fff87b1e0083337658c98c5c8abed1",
    "ut": 1647739508,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "The International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          15
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Sri Lanka Cricket - reflects the decadent country mindset!",
    "source": "www.islandcricket.lk",
    "snippet": "Victory and defeat are a part and parcel of sporting events. So, there was no grave reason to cry about the result of the last test series in India. What produces tears however, was the abject manner in which the Sri Lanka team folded up within a space of three days.",
    "url": "https://www.islandcricket.lk/news/sri-lanka-cricket-reflects-the-decadent-country-mindset/",
    "url_hash": "49d011686530b9f8539896a7c077a25a",
    "ut": 1647739508,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "India",
        "start_end": [
          30,
          31
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          44,
          46
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "three days",
        "start_end": [
          53,
          55
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Sri Lanka fuel queue claims first death: report",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "ECONOMYNEXT - A person waiting in a queue to buy kerosene (paraffin) in the central Sri Lanka district of Kandy has died after collapsing, a media report said. Sri Lanka's Sirasa television said the 71 year old person was believed to be a resident of ...",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-fuel-queue-claims-first-death-report-91855/",
    "url_hash": "936bacd6e9fc2ac83a21efdbba711914",
    "ut": 1647741326,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Kandy",
        "start_end": [
          21,
          22
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Sri Lanka's",
        "start_end": [
          32,
          35
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Sirasa",
        "start_end": [
          35,
          36
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "71 year old",
        "start_end": [
          39,
          42
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Sapugaskanda refinery to stop operations from tomorrow: CPC Chairman",
    "source": "www.dailymirror.lk",
    "snippet": "The fuel refinery operations at the Sapugaskanda oil refinery will be suspended from tomorrow, Ceylon Petrolium Corporation (CPC) Chairman Sumith Wijesinghe said. ..",
    "url": "https://www.dailymirror.lk/latest_news/Sapugaskanda-refinery-to-stop-operations-from-tomorrow-CPC-Chairman/342-233425",
    "url_hash": "68d9d66b7bc0f78530c80c918e3dd410",
    "ut": 1647742115,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sapugaskanda",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          7
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "DATE",
        "text": "tomorrow",
        "start_end": [
          13,
          14
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Ceylon Petrolium Corporation",
        "start_end": [
          15,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Sumith Wijesinghe",
        "start_end": [
          22,
          24
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Cyclone Asani update: Evacuation process starts; fishermen alerted. Check date, time and how to track",
    "source": "www.livemint.com",
    "snippet": "The storm is likely to bring extremely heavy rainfall to Andaman and Nicobar Island. Meanwhile, fishermen have already been warned not to venture into the sea.",
    "url": "https://www.livemint.com/news/india/cyclone-asani-update-evacuation-process-starts-fishermen-alerted-check-date-time-and-how-to-track-11647700205827.html",
    "url_hash": "6b75a0dbbf2285140d290b59ebe73ea3",
    "ut": 1647744000,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Andaman",
        "start_end": [
          10,
          11
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Nicobar Island",
        "start_end": [
          12,
          14
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "'He was Superman': Eddie McGuire's tribute to Shane Warne at funeral",
    "source": "au.sports.yahoo.com",
    "snippet": "The TV personality was among a host of high-profile names to attend Shane Warne's private funeral in Melbourne. Find out more here.",
    "url": "https://au.sports.yahoo.com/shane-warne-2022-eddie-mcguire-funeral-tribute-cricket-icon-025916167.html",
    "url_hash": "9a75f99dda69fd446726364d28a10244",
    "ut": 1647745759,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Shane Warne's",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          17
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Melbourne",
        "start_end": [
          20,
          21
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Sri Lanka IMF deal attempts were blocked by Vasudeva Nanayakkara: Minister",
    "source": "economynext.com",
    "snippet": "Previous attempts to go for an International Monetary Fund bailout was blocked at cabinet by Water Minister Vasudeva Nanayakkara, who threatened to resign, a government minister has said.",
    "url": "https://economynext.com/sri-lanka-imf-deal-attempts-were-blocked-by-vasudeva-nanayakkara-minister-91856/",
    "url_hash": "282e36bcdc953d4dd3049ba5ea60bcef",
    "ut": 1647745776,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "International Monetary Fund",
        "start_end": [
          6,
          9
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "PERSON",
        "text": "Vasudeva Nanayakkara",
        "start_end": [
          17,
          19
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Interview | My book discusses the notion of power that conditions human minds: 'Alpha' author TD Ramakrishnan",
    "source": "www.msn.com",
    "snippet": "The book, On the surface, TD Ramakrishna's 'Alpha' is a straight-forward novella about rejecting societal norms. But in reality, it's an intrinsic study of how politics, intellectualism, and society g",
    "url": "https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/other/interview-my-book-discusses-the-notion-of-power-that-conditions-human-minds-e2-80-98alpha-e2-80-99-author-td-ramakrishnan/ar-AAVh4gA",
    "url_hash": "3aa3fb0e0960e7979abb6ed43af64778",
    "ut": 1647746839,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "TD Ramakrishna's '",
        "start_end": [
          7,
          11
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "date": "2022-03-20",
    "title": "Dharmadasa Siriwardhana",
    "source": "dailynews.lk",
    "snippet": "Rathgama Police arrested a coconut seller for selling packets of heroin in coconuts in the Panvila New Colony in Rathgama.She was arrested along with 7.8 grams of heroin, Police said.The woman had...",
    "url": "https://dailynews.lk/line/dharmadasa-siriwardhana",
    "url_hash": "ef3f9ecb1064a9b0b9543a7c8857e652",
    "ut": 1647750279,
    "ent_info_list": [
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "Rathgama Police",
        "start_end": [
          0,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "ORG",
        "text": "the Panvila New Colony",
        "start_end": [
          14,
          18
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "GPE",
        "text": "Rathgama",
        "start_end": [
          19,
          20
        ]
      },
      {
        "label": "QUANTITY",
        "text": "7.8 grams",
        "start_end": [
          26,
          28
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]